Saber!
Saber...
You're safe.
I made it in-
Saber!
How...
am I here again?
Who are you?
What in the hell...
are you?
On-site investigations are continuing,
but as the police entered the destruction site
this morning... PART OF MT. ENZO COLLAPSED
but as the police entered the destruction site this
morning... PART OF MT. ENZO COLLAPSED Um, Senpai...
they found some of the temple buildings
have collapsed. PART OF MT. ENZO COLLAPSED
they found some of the temple buildings have
collapsed. PART OF IVIT. ENZO COLLAPSED Senpai?
We'll take you to the scene. PART
OF MT. ENZO COLLAPSED Senpai?
We'll take you to the scene.
PART OF MT. ENZO COLLAPSED
Y-Yeah, What is it?
I'm here in front of Ryudou Temple,
Oh, it's just...
located at Mt. Enzo in the Miyama area...
located at Mt. Enzo in the Miyama area... Saber
left for her home all of a sudden, didn't she?
Saber left for her home
all of a sudden, didn't she?
The site is cordoned... Saber left for
her home all of a sudden, didn't she?
The site is cordoned...
Yeah.
and we are unable to see inside.
The collapse occurred in the building
and the area around the pond.
But now, The collapse occurred in the
building and the area around the pond.
But now,
you no longer have to go out at night, right?
So, you're not going to be
in danger anymore, right?
No.
You're wrong about that, Sakura.
I wasn't tagging along with Saber.
Saber was the one
who was tagging along with me.
I might be going out more often now.
But I don't want you to wait for me
at the entrance.
That's right.
It's not over yet.
The one I must fight...
is still in this city.
ROAD UNDER MAINTENANCE
LANE CLOSED AT FUYUKI
ON-RAMP DUE TO ACCIDENT
ALL LANES NOW CLEAR
New City.
Central Park.
Ryudou Temple.
What is the shadow-like thing after?
And what is its relationship with Zouken?
Is it working for him?
Or is he just taking advantage of it?
I may have to ask Tohsaka about this.
What the...
You're still alive, Big Brother!
Tell me your name.
Your name, Big Brother.
S-Sure.
I'm Shirou. Shirou Emiya.
Shirou!
Shirou! Shirou! Right?
Yep!
H-Hold on!
Hold on a second!
We're enemies, aren't we, Illyasviel?
Just call me Ill ya!
Masters can only fight
each other at night.
I came here to chat with you, Shirou.
Look, you suddenly hacked away at me,
and now you wanna chat with me?
What? That was just an accident!
It was all because you jumped in recklessly
even though you're weak!
I could kill you right here, right now, too.
Without Saber, you'd be killed in an instant!
Besides,
I've been waiting for this chance
all this time.
So, don't I deserve a little chat?
So, you're living
in the castle in the forest.
All alone?
No, with Sella and Liz.
I sneaked out behind Sella's back
just to see you!
You should feel honored!
Oh, I guess.
Then, can I ask you one more thing?
Does the name Kiritsugu Emiya
ring any bells?
Ill ya?
Don't know.
I don't know a name like that.
I'm going home.
Ill ya!
Huh?
Emiya?
Tohsaka!
Good timing!
I wanted to have a chat with you, too.
We could chat at school, too, you know.
Archer, can you make us some tea?
You don't want to?
What's with that face?
Jeez, fine!
Huh?
This is...
What are you doing?
Now, let's discuss our game plan.
I have to get dinner ready.
Why didn't you tell me earlier
that Sakura had a fever?
'Cause you didn't let me interrupt you!
It's open.
Sakura, are you awake?
Emiya?
Jeez!
Shinji! Let go of Sakura!
Shinji!
Don't worry, Sakura.
I won't kill Emiya or anything.
I just want him
to feel a little pain, that's all.
Fight with Rider.
If you survive,
I don't mind letting go of her.
Get him, Rider!
If you were going to fight,
you shouldn't have come alone.
What's wrong, Emiya?
It'd be so boring
if you croaked too easily!
You won since you have good endurance.
Good! Now, don't hold back anymore.
Just kill him off right now, Rider!
Stop it, Big Brother-
Sakura...
Senpai!
Wh...
Why?
Stagecraft...
Rider!
Kill him!
T-Tohsaka?
Why?
Emiya and I have formed a coalition.
It just so happens
that we were together all day today.
Because you used Sakura as bait,
you completely made yourself my enemy.
Sakura...
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura,
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura!
Why do you care about someone like her?
I was the one who became a Master!
Stand up, Rider!
Damn you!
Don't...
Rider, please don't...
Stop right now!
— Sakura!
- Emiya, get down!
You gotta be kidding.
This is...
really Rider?
Good going, Rider!
Keep at it and get rid of them all!
Hey, Rider!
I see.
Matou's bloodline is already obsolete
and can't produce anyone
who can handle Magecraft.
I'd thought Zouken was the one
who summoned Rider
and had lent her to Shinji.
But it was actually a lot simpler than that.
Tohsaka?
In the current state of the Matou family,
the one most fit to become a Master...
...is the rightful heir of Matou,
their current Mage. And that's you,
Sakura.
Sakura...
is a Master?
The transfer of Command Spells...
A Command Spell for Rider
to obey Shinji Matou's orders.
With that, Shinji has become Rider's Master.
Hey...
Hey... Meanwhile, you lost
your authority as her Master
Meanwhile, you lost
and became an ordinary Mage.
Who are you guys looking at?
Because the Matou family is the one
that created Command Spells,
such a trick was possible,
wasn't it, Sakura?
Hey!
Look over here!
We haven't finished yet!
One more time, Sakura!
Give me control over her one more time!
Why are you acting
so goody-goody after all this?
You have one more Command Spell!
Use that, and...
Shinji, Rider will become free from you
if you don't have Command Spells.
And when that happens, even if you make
a False Attendant's Writings,
it'll quickly be burned up,
and that'll be it for you.
Because you were only controlling her
with borrowed Command Spells,
you were never a Master to begin with.
Shinji...
That's right.
I knew that.
I knew that! I knew that!
I knew that!
I knew all along, from the beginning,
I'd never fit this role!
Since I'm not a Master,
you should do it.
Kill them all in my place, Sakura.
No, Big Brother.
Let's stop it here!
You broke your promise.
You said you wouldn't kill Senpai!
So, please...
Then, fine.
Why don't you just...
die?
Sakura!
Senpai...
No!
Don't look at me!
Sakura...
Looks like she can't control it.
Get away from this place!
If we carelessly feed her
magical energy, we can't revert her!
Please don't get in our way.
Pull back, Rider!
Your master is running out of control!
At this rate, she'll use up
all her magical energy and self-destruct!
It simply means she must take in
more magical energy than she's expending.
So, a change in your master
hasn't changed your rotten nature!
A bounded field?
Stop it.
Stop this already, Rider!
I...
didn't summon you because I wanted
to do something like this!
I cannot abide by that command.
I prioritize your life
more than anything else.
No way! Mystic Eyes of Petrification?
Tohsaka!
2000s!
Saki...
Pa."
Sakura!
Emiya,
are you all right?
Tohsaka!
So, you're finally awake.
I just finished treatment on Sakura Matou.
How's Sakura?
Is Sakura all right?
Calm down.
We brought her here with Rider's help.
Kirei, how is Sakura doing?
She's not stable yet,
but her life's been spared for now.
Hold on a second!
What happened
to all of your Magical Crests?
I had no choice but to use them all
for the treatment of Sakura Matou.
All of them?
And the result of that treatment...
Crest Worms?
What the hell are they, um...
Just think of them
as living Magical Circuits.
A Crest Worm, once it sinks its teeth in,
infiltrates every last inch of your body,
and voraciously devours your spirit.
It pierces through
and lubricates skin with its mucus
and feeds itself by stimulating
then decomposing the part of the brain
controlling pleasure.
As a result,
women swarmed by these bugs
are completely violated
in both mind and body,
and thus destroyed.
Sakura Matou is also-
Stop it!
I thought you'd need some explanation.
As long as that thing is inside her body,
her magical energy, which is her life energy,
is being sucked away limitless.
If you leave her like that,
it will ultimately kill her.
The operation was a success, right?
Not completely.
The worms accumulated for 11 years.
If we forcefully pry them out of her,
her body won't last.
To completely be rid of them,
that's something you'd actually
have to rely on the Holy Grail for.
Tohsaka?
As the one in charge of Fuyuki,
I'll take care of her.
Take care of her?
You mean Sakura Matou?
Yes. I can't allow Mages
who can't control their powers to live.
She is already nothing
more than a Master gone mad.
Even if...
she is your biological little sister?
Little sister?
The Tohsakas originally had two children.
But Magecraft is taught only to one child.
I inherited the Magecraft
of the Tohsakas.
The Matou or Makiri family's bloodline
had already been severed.
So, Sakura was adopted by them
as the heir of the family.
Then...
Sakura and I are sisters by blood.
Though, we've never called
each other as such.
Hold on, Tohsaka!
Then, all the more reason to...
If I leave her alone like this,
the same thing will happen again.
To innocent bystanders, next time.
No matter who they may be.
That's why I...
am going to kill her.
You win, Sakura.
So, I'll give you this.
This is the second time...
I've received something important...
from someone dear to me!
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
Sakura. ..
I've gotta find her before Tohsaka does.
But...
after finding Sakura,
what am I...
Good evening, Shirou.
Didn't you say we fight at night?
No. You're no longer a Master.
I know everything, you see.
Rider's Master has also fallen,
so only two more remain.
You want to save Rider's Master,
but you can't find her, right?
Shut up!
Shirou, you look like you're going to cry.
Ill ya, aren't you mad at me?
No, I'm not.
I'm on your side, Shirou.
On my side?
You asked me this morning...
about Kiritsugu... I actually knew him.
The reason I was born
is to win the Holy Grail War,
but my own personal objective
was to kill Kiritsugu and you, Shirou.
But...
if you want to protect
someone dear to you,
I'll be on your side!
It's only natural to protect
the person you're in love with.
I know that!
I've... now lost all places I can return to!
Sakura...
Senpai?
Let's go home. You're not fully
over your cold yet, right?
I can't go home.
That thing earlier...
It wasn't a poison or anything.
It's only an elixir
that heightens the senses.
With only some of that,
I lost myself and hurt you!
I'm not hurt at all.
I'm totally okay with something like that.
I am a Mage of the Matou family,
and kept that fact
hidden from you for all this time!
And I didn't tell you
I became a Master, either.
The reason why I was going
to your place so much
was because I was scared
to stand up to Grandfather!
I said I was helping you out,
but I've been fooling you all along!
Always...
I always thought...
I'm not someone
who can stay at your side.
So, I kept thinking
that I'd end all of this today,
and, starting tomorrow,
I'd pretend I didn't know you.
That I'd ignore you even if we pass
each other in the campus hallway,
and pretend I didn't know you after school.
That I'd go home all by myself
and forget everything
that has happened up until now!
But I couldn't do it!
It was scarier than the moment when I put
a knife to my wrist to commit suicide.
I was scared of deceiving you,
and I was scared of stopping the deceit!
Everything around me was just scary!
I was no longer able to take
even one step forward!
I just didn't know what to do at all!
I wanted to protect my time
together with you going forward, as well.
For me...
For me, that was the only thing...
that means anything to me.
The person I want to protect...
The person who is important to me...
If I don't want that person
to cry anymore...
If nobody is going to reprimand Sakura,
and she has to reprimand herself...
I'll lead her by the hand
and make sure to take her
to a brighter place.
Even if nobody were to forgive her...
I will...
continue to forgive you in your place.
So don't cry anymore.
I fully understand now
that you are a bad person.
I don't know when I'll lose sight
of myself again, like I did earlier.
I'm sure I'll do something
that'll be simply irreparable.
So, where are you saying
someone like me can go home to?
This is your home, Sakura.
I...
I'm...
not a virgin.
My first time was quite a long time ago.
That's not all.
Ever since that first time,
my body has been touched
by unnatural things.
I don't deserve to be protected by you!
I will protect you.
No matter what happens,
even if you try to kill yourself,
I'll protect you, Sakura.
Senpai...
I will become a hero of justice
just for you, Sakura!
You can't do that, Senpai.
I'm sure I will end up hurting you!
I will hurt you...
Let's go home.
Sakura...
Big Sis...
Tohsaka-senpai...
Shirou Emiya...
If you kept the belief
you've been sticking with, continue to do so.
The results are obvious.
But if you're going to choose
a different path,
there is no future for Shirou Emiya.
You will end up losing
anything and everything.
You must be tired.
Take your time and rest up.
O-Okay.
What's wrong, Sakura?
Do you have a fever?
You were in the rain for so long.
I-It's not a cold.
My magical energy is a bit...
lacking.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Um...
Would you like to...
No! I'll be fine if you could give me
a small amount of your blood.
S-Sure.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I-I see.
Well then, g-good night.
Okay.
I shouldn't go any further!
I can't contaminate him
any more than this!
Sakura, can you make a soup stock?
Okay!
What about the spinach?
Let's dress it with sesame today.
Sakura, eggs.
Here!
- Thank you for the meal!
It's been a while
since we did this last time.
Yes.
You're not gonna eat?
It's okay. Don't be shy.
We Servants don't require
the intake of nutrients the same way you do.
Is that so?
Saber used to eat a lot.
Your way doesn't suit me.
Well then,
if that's the case...
For our strategy from now on...
I will have Sakura win,
and have her use the Holy Grail.
But I think Sakura had better not go outside.
It'd be dangerous
if she saw Zouken in person.
I believe that idea is correct.
However, how will you defeat that Mage?
I think we should cooperate
with the other Masters.
Who else is left?
Tohsaka's Archer, Sakura's Rider...
Zouken has his Assassin in tow.
Other than that, Illya's...
Berserker.
Is it going to be all right?
Yeah, probably.
Don't go outside, okay?
Are you regretting this?
I can't have regrets
after coming this far.
Rider, if things get dangerous,
bring Senpai back home.
But Sakura...
I think the one we should be careful of is...
that priest instead of the elderly man.
Right.
I actually think so, as well.
But rest assured, Rider.
Because there's no way
he can win against me.
Well then...
Lipase!
I got it! All I have to do
is keep him from going outside.
That way, he won't be
in any danger again, right?
Huh?
What was I just thinking about?
Talk about rough trekking.
I guess it wants me to follow, huh?
Huh?
It's gone.
What happened to this?
You sure are a cowardly Servant,
much like your master.
I can't feel any intent
to fight against us.
Do you value your life that much?
Of course I do.
My wish is for eternal life.
Look at this body!
With each moment it rots,
emitting a foul odor,
losing the knowledge
I have stashed away within.
Do you understand the pain
of rotting away while you're still alive?
No human is fearless of death.
If that was going to grant me my wish,
I would run around the entire world
killing every human one by one.
I'm disgusted.
You have lost sight
of things that much, Makiri?
Remember again
what we earnestly wished for.
Remember where our thirst
for achieving the miracle came from.
And why we've been striving to reach
the point where we're not human...
while keeping our human bodies.
Quite the words from a mere puppet.
Of course they've 'are-programmed you, huh?
Playtime is now over.
I, Zouken Matou, will take
the Einzberns' Holy Grail.
No, don't, Berserker!
Tohsaka! Why?
I never thought you'd come up
with the same idea, Emiya.
You gotta be kidding me!
Get away from there!
If that thing gets you,
you won't be able to come back!
The score has been settled.
I'll leave you to do the rest.
Don't let the Einzbern girl go
after all this effort.
Berserker!
Ill ya!
Jeez, Archer...
Berserker...
I will be your opponent.
Archer!
I'm counting on you.
This is the end.
A genuine Heroic Spirit...
could not fight
the Cursed Boundary Layer of that thing.
At present, you are not much different
from the phantoms filling this forest.
Berserker!
This doesn't look good.
Berserker...
Berserker!
No... No!
My duties are complete.
I will leave you to do the rest.
How gracious of you.
I can regain the points I have lost.
Saber!
Ill ya!
That's far enough.
You're of no use.
You can't kill a puny boy
unless you do a sneak attack, can you?
Pathetic.
How could you come here?
Who knows?
Archer!
Hurry!
If that thing catches up, it's all over!
We'll talk later. Run, brat!
Now that you've taken Illya's hand,
protect her until the very end!
Let's go!
HOW?