/Huh? I can't taste anything./
/He's so warm./
/It's okay. I can still feel him./
/I wish this moment could last forever.../
She went for a lovely walk.
Her bobbing head was clear, with no definite goal in mind.
And she shook from side to side.
Go, go.
And she sang with a chuckle.
And the empty limbs rolled along the ground like paper balloons.
And floating through the air would have to wait until she grew up.
Go, go.
Someone came up to her and squeaked.
It roared at her in laughter.
She had no reason to be scared of it!
The shrill laughter echoed throughout the room,
so her empty stomach growled.
You're looking lively.
This is why I told you to die the last time we met.
So shiny and pretty...
This has been postponed long enough.
Accept that this is an act of mercy.
What? You still have life in you?
To think that your body had changed, too, and not just your shadow.
You dare expect me to kneel?
Mongrel!
Have you truly gone that far?
Did you see that?
Huh?
Shirou!
Come to the living room! Right now!
At 10:08 PM today, there was a widespread blackout near Shinto Station.
Police have received reports of neighbors disappearing, going missing, or vanishing into thin air,
among other unexplained incidents, around this time.
Sakura!
Don't move. I'll go get the first aid kit!
Saku...
/Don't notice it./
/Stop./
/Don't think they look alike./
It is currently estimated that there are over sixty victims.
There are forty buildings whose residents' whereabouts are presently unknown.
How's Sakura?
Alive.
But...
Is there something different about this?
Sakura's body looks like it's put together well on the surface,
but the muscles in her arms and legs are in tatters.
She's definitely died at least once.
I don't know who did it, but the pain might have destroyed not just her body, but her brain, too.
We don't have a second to lose in defeating Zouken and the shadow.
Let's do whatever we can.
But, Shirou,
if Zouken and that shadow turn out to be two completely different things,
what will you do?
Good morning.
Are you still in there, Sakura?
Where did you get those souls from?
Assassin and Rider are still alive.
I'd be surprised if you were full already.
Sakura, do you know what's going to happen to you?
No. What's going to happen to me?
You'll die. You can't be saved.
I'm home! I got some time to be here!
Huh? Shirou? You around?
Who's that?
I swear, what happened to Shirou?
He needs to be here for you.
Hey, don't push yourself.
Senpai said he would protect me.
But I'm sorry.
It was my fault his dreams were destroyed
Why?
Because I'm a bad person.
Shirou's the kind of boy who'll get mad at you for doing bad things.
You want to fix your bad parts, don't you?
Yes.
Then everything's fine.
Besides, Shirou's dream is to be a superhero, right?
Of course he'd have someone he wants to protect.
But shouldn't he treat everyone equally?
If Shirou's trying to be like Kiritsugu-san,
then it's okay to have someone special.
Kiritsugu-san played favorites too, you know?
Even after he started living in this town,
he traveled abroad over and over.
He did it until he couldn't even move.
There must have been someone he really wanted to see.
It hurts when you can't see your special someone.
Even if you're a superhero.
So make sure you stay by Shirou's side, okay?
/Will you betray him?/
/Will you betray your past self?/
Hey.
Stop.
/If you will betray him,/
/you must.../
Stop!
No.
I couldn't...
Emiya Shirou, I presume?
My magus wishes to speak to you.
You arrived faster than I expected,
son of Emiya.
Zouken...
I only have one thing to say to you.
Let Sakura go, right now.
Let her go?
I suppose that is one way of putting it.
Emiya Shirou, I called you here to ask a favor of you.
I wish for you to kill the shadow.
Isn't that thing in cahoots with you?
Cahoots?
That thing cannot be reasoned with.
As of last night, I cannot even pacify it.
Oh, but before that, I must tell you what that shadow is.
In a word, it is the contents of the Holy Grail.
Wills overflowing from the gate we call the Grail.
That is the shadow.
The shadow and... a gate...
I told you to kill the shadow, but that will be difficult.
However, you can kill the gate.
It would see right through myself or the Tohsaka girl.
Servants are its feed.
Stop.
I planted a shard of the Grail in it
and raised it as the Matous' Holy Grail for ten years. The only one who can kill it is...
Stop!
Surely you realize by now
that it is similar to Sakura.
That doll who does nothing but exist
will die at the hands of the man she loves.
She could ask for no better end.
We are running out of time.
When Sakura's consciousness grows faint, the Holy Grail she unconsciously borrowed
will rise to the surface.
The disaster from ten years ago will be recreated.
If you wish to save Sakura, you must endure until the time limit for the Holy Grail War runs out.
According to precedent, that should be about four more days.
What do you think?
Will Sakura be able to hold out?
She will.
She absolutely will!
But the same cannot be said for others.
She may have eaten her fill last night,
but it will strike again as early as tomorrow.
How many days will it take for her to finish eating the people of this city?
Surely you know.
Strike down evil for the sake of the many.
If you wish to become Emiya Kiritsugu,
then Matou Sakura is your enemy.
Sakura, you awake?
Yes.
Good morning, Senpai.
Hey, Sakura.
Is there anything you wanna do when this battle's over?
I can't really think of anything.
As long as I'm with you, it doesn't matter what we do.
Then how about we go somewhere fun?
Where do you wanna go?
Well, I suppose I'd like to go flower-viewing...
All right.
It's a promise.
/I'll create a warm illusion with a frozen heart./
/When winter passes and a new spring comes,/
/we'll both go see the cherry blossoms./
/Yes./
/When spring comes.../
/Senpai./
/My name is Matou Sakura./
/This makes the second time I've received something important.../
/Here, have this./
/I'll.../
/A superhero?/
/Senpai.../
/I wanted to keep protecting the time I spend with you./
/I wish this moment could last forever.../
/Senpai./
/Senpai!/
/Senpai.../
/Will you betray him?/
Yeah. I will.
/Thank you, Senpai./
/You've given me so much./
/Thank you, Nee-san./
/It made me so happy to call you that./
/Fujimura-sensei, thank you for everything./
/I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise./
Rider, thank you for not killing Senpai.
Sakura...
This is my last Command Spell.
Please, Rider...
/I'll be the one to stop Grandfather./
/It's too late,/
/but I can't cause any more trouble than I already have./
Sakura, morning...
Wait, what?
Hi there, traitor.
Took you long enough to come home.
Um, Nii-san, I...
Hold this for me.
It's nothing dangerous.
It's beautiful...
You're something else, Sakura.
You might even surpass Tohsaka someday.
Nii-san...
Get off your high horse.
You're nothing but my doll.
/I've made another mistake./
/That's why something horrible's going to happen to me./
/It's okay. I just have to put up with it for a while, just like always./
/Put up with it, put up with it, put up with it, put up with it.../
Sakura.
No!
No. I belong to Senpai now!
What?
Looks like he's trained you good!
No!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
/Why does this always happen to me?/
Behave yourself!
Hey!
/I've thought this for so long./
/I've hated him for so long./
/Why does the world around me hate me so much?/
Hey, I'd better tell Emiya, too.
I'll tell him how much you've clung to me so far
and how dirty you are in bed!
/The world would be better off without him./
Nii-san...
Sakura!
I told you before. I'll be your personal superhero.
So grit your teeth!
09 - Today's Headline
Partial Cave-in on Enzou Mountain, Fuyuki-shi
27 - Road Work Ahead
35 - Accident at Fuyuki Entrance
Lanes Closed Ahead
37 - Fuyuki Entrance Lanes Now Open
21:25 - Multiple Bodies Found in Shinto Central Park
29:39 - Multiple Missing Persons in Shinto
55:51 - Preview
56:39 - The Final Chapter
56:48 - Coming to theaters Spring 2020
Shirou: Saber!
Saber!
Saber...
Thank goodness. You're okay...
Saber!
Why am I back here?
/What are you?/
Um, Senpai.
Senpai?
Oh, what is it?
Well, Saber-san returned to her country rather suddenly.
Yeah.
But now you don't have to go out at night, right?
You don't have to put yourself in danger, right?
Actually,
you're wrong about that, Sakura.
I wasn't tagging along with Saber's errands.
She was tagging along with mine.
I might be out of the house even more now.
But can you stop waiting at the entrance when I'm out late?
/Yeah. It's not over yet./
/There's still someone in this town I have to fight./
/Shinto./
/Central Park./
/Ryuudou Temple./
/What's that shadow-looking thing after?/
/How's it connected to Zouken?/
/Is it working for him?/
/No, he's just using it./
/I'd better ask Tohsaka, too./
What?
Oh, you're alive, Onii-chan!
Tell me your name.
Your name, Onii-chan.
Oh, I'm Shirou. Emiya Shirou.
Shirou. Shirou. You're Shirou!
Got it.
Hey!
Hold on a sec!
We're enemies, remember, Illyasviel?
Just call me Illya.
Masters are only allowed to fight at night, right?
I wanna talk to you.
Look, chopping someone in half isn't the best way to make 'em wanna talk to you.
What are you talking about? That's different.
You're the one who came flying at me even though you're so weak.
I could kill you right now if I wanted to.
Without Saber, you wouldn't last a second.
And...
I've been waiting all this time.
You can give me this, can't you?
So you live in the castle in the forest, Illya?
Alone?
Sella and Liz live with me.
I had to pull a fast one on Sella to come meet you today.
You should be honored.
Uh-huh...
Can I ask you one more question?
Do you know the name Kiritsugu?
Illya?
I don't know. Never heard of it.
I don't know.
I'm going home.
Illya!
Huh?
Emiya-kun?
Tohsaka.
I wanted to have a chat with you, too.
Couldn't we have just talked at school?
Archer, can you make us some tea?
You don't want to?
What's with that face?
Jeez, fine!
Huh?
This is...
What are you doing?
Come on, let's get strategizing.
I need to get dinner ready.
Sakura's got a fever? You should've said so sooner!
You wouldn't let me get a word in edgewise!
It's unlocked.
Sakura, you awake?
Emiya-kun?
Shinji! Let Sakura go!
Shinji!
Don't worry, Sakura. I won't kill Emiya.
But I do need to hurt him a little.
Fight Rider.
If you make it out okay, I'll let her go.
Get him, Rider.
If you intended to fight,
you should not have come here alone.
What's wrong, Emiya?
It won't be any fun if you go down this easily!
Your endurance has won you this battle.
Looking good. Time to stop holding back.
Go ahead and fight him to the death, Rider!
Nii-san, no!
Sakura.
Senpai...
Why...
Why?
Magecraft...
Rider!
Kill him!
Huh?
T-Tohsaka...
Why?
Emiya-kun and I formed an alliance.
We've been together all day today.
Now that you're using Sakura like a tool,
you're nothing but my enemy.
Sakura...
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura,
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura!
Who gives a shit about her?
I'm the one who became a Master!
Stand up, Rider!
You useless...
No...
Rider, no...
No more of this!
Sakura--
Emiya-kun, get down!
No way...
This is Rider?
There you go, Rider!
Go on and take 'em all down!
Hey, Rider!
Yeah.
The Matou bloodline has dried up.
They can't produce anyone who can use magecraft.
I thought Zouken had summoned Rider and given her to Shinji.
But it was much more simple than that.
Tohsaka?
The most suitable person to be a Master in the Matou family now...
is the Matous' legitimate heir, their magus of this generation. You, Sakura.
Sakura's a Master?
You transferred Command Spells and used one to make her obey Shinji's orders, huh?
That's how Shinji became Rider's Master,
Hey.
and in the meantime, you lost your rights as a Master,
becoming just another magus.
What are you all looking at?
That little trick was only possible because the Matous were the ones who created the Command Spells.
Right, Sakura?
Hey! Look at me!
It's not over yet!
One more time, Sakura!
Give me command rights again!
Why are you trying to play the good girl?
You still have one Command Spell! Use that!
Shinji, if she runs out of Command Spells, Rider will be free.
If that happens, even if you make a tome, it'll just burn up immediately.
You were controlling her with borrowed Command Spells.
You were never a Master in the first place.
Shinji...
Yeah, I knew.
I knew, I knew, I knew!
I knew I was never cut out for it!
So you have to do it.
You kill them instead of me, Sakura.
No, Nii-san.
Let's stop this.
You broke your promise.
You said you wouldn't kill Senpai!
So stop it!
All right, fine.
You can go ahead and die.
Sakura!
Senpai... no...
Don't look at me...
Sakura...
Looks like she can't control it.
Get away from here!
If we hit her with mana the wrong way, she won't turn back!
Don't get in my way.
Listen to me, Rider!
Your lord has gone out of control.
At this rate, she'll burn through her mana and die!
Then we need only provide her with mana faster than she can lose it.
Looks like changing your lord didn't change who you are!
A bounded field?
Stop...
Stop it, Rider...
I didn't summon you to do things like this!
I can't obey that order.
I will prioritize your life above all else.
No way...
Mystic Eyes of petrification!
Tohsaka!
No!
...saka...
Sakura!
Emiya-kun, you okay?
Tohsaka!
Awake at last, I see.
I have just finished treating Matou Sakura.
Sakura... Is Sakura okay?
Calm down.
I brought her and Rider here.
Kirei, how's Sakura's condition?
Not stable, but her life is no longer in immediate danger.
Wait a second. What happened to your Magic Crest?
I had no choice but to use it all to treat Matou Sakura.
All of it?
Now, as for the results of my treatment...
Crest Worms?
What are those? Uh...
Think of them as living Magic Circuits.
Once a Crest Worm sinks its teeth into you,
it penetrates the entire body, eating your life away.
It pierces and dampens the skin with its mucus,
sating its hunger by elevating and destroying the pleasure centers.
As a result, any woman preyed upon by these insects
will be entirely violated in both mind and body.
Matou Sakura is no excep--
Stop it!
I thought you needed an explanation.
As long as those things exist in her body, her life force, her mana, will be leeched without end.
Left alone, she will lose her life.
You said the surgery succeeded!
Not entirely.
She has been this way for eleven years.
One wrong move with the extraction, and her body will give out.
To fully remove the Crest Worms would truly require the Holy Grail.
Tohsaka...
As Fuyuki's supervisor, I have to dispose of her.
Dispose of her? Matou Sakura?
Yes. A magus who can't control her power can't be allowed to live.
She's just an insane Master now.
Even if she is your sister by blood?
Sister?
The Tohsakas actually had two children.
But magecraft can only be passed down to one.
I inherited the magecraft of the Tohsakas.
Sakura was adopted by the dying Matou family as the heir to the Makiris.
Then--
Sakura and I are blood-related sisters.
Not that we've ever called each other that.
Wait, Tohsaka.
That's all the more reason to...
If we leave her like this, the same thing will happen again.
This time, it'll happen indiscriminately to random bystanders.
That's why I have to kill her.
You win, Sakura.
Here, have this.
This makes the second time I've received something important from someone special.
Sakura. ..
I have to find Sakura before Tohsaka does.
But when I do find her, what...
Good evening, Shirou.
I thought we were supposed to fight at night.
You're not a Master anymore.
I know everything that happened.
Rider's Master collapsed, and now there's two left.
You want to save Rider's Master, but you can't find her, right?
Shut up!
You look like you're about to cry.
Illya, aren't you mad at me?
No, I'm not.
I'm on your side.
You're on my side?
When you asked me about Kiritsugu this morning, I lied. I know him.
I was born to win the Holy Grail War, but my personal goal was to kill you and Kiritsugu.
But now, if you want to protect someone precious to you,
I'll be on your side.
It's only natural to protect the girl you like, right?
I know all about it.
Now I've lost all the places I can go home to...
Sakura.
Senpai...
Let's go home.
You're still not over your cold, right?
I can't.
That liquid wasn't poison or something.
It was just medicine to heighten my senses.
That's all it took for me to lose my mind and hurt you!
I'm not hurt.
I'm totally fine.
I'm a magus of the Matou family. I hid that from you.
I never told you I was a Master, either.
I only started going to your house because I was scared of my grandfather!
I lied to you the whole time, pretending I just wanted to help you!
I always, always thought
that I didn't deserve to be by your side.
So many times, I'd think of quitting and pretending I didn't know you the next day.
Even if I saw you in the hallway, I'd walk right past you.
After school, I'd ignore you.
Then I'd go home alone and forget all about everything.
But I couldn't!
It was scarier than when I tried to cut my wrists with a knife.
I was too scared to deceive you, and too scared to stop!
Everything around me scared me.
I couldn't take a single step.
I didn't know what to do!
I wanted to keep protecting the time I spend with you.
That was the only thing in my life that had any meaning.
/What I want to protect./
/What's precious to me./
/If I don't want her to cry anymore,/
/if nobody will blame Sakura, if she has to do it herself,/
/I'll take her by the hand and bring her into the sunlight./
/Even if nobody else forgives her,/
I'll keep forgiving you in your place.
Come on, don't cry.
I know full well what a bad person you are.
I have no idea when I'll lose my mind like I did today.
I'm sure I'll do something unforgivable.
What kind of home could there be for me?
This is your home.
I... I...
I'm not a virgin.
My first time was long, long ago.
On top of that, ever since then,
these mysterious things have kept touching me.
I don't deserve to be protected by you!
I'll protect you.
No matter what happens, even if you try to kill yourself,
I'll protect you, Sakura.
Senpai...
I'll be your personal superhero.
No, Senpai.
If you do that, I'll end up hurting you.
You'll get hurt.
Let's go home.
Sakura.
Nee-sama...
Tohsaka-senpai...
Emiya Shirou.
If you plan to uphold your convictions, then so be it.
I know how that ends.
But if you choose a different path, then Emiya Shirou has no future.
You will lose absolutely everything.
You must be tired.
Get a good night's sleep.
Yes.
What's wrong, Sakura?
You have a fever?
Well, you /were/ in the rain for a while.
It's... not a cold.
I'm running low on mana.
Uh, is there anything I can do for you?
Um...
Can you...
No, all I need is a little bit of your blood.
Uh-huh...
Will this work?
Yes.
You good now?
Great.
Then, uh...
Good night.
No.
Any more than this,
and I'll just hurt Senpai...
Sakura, can you get the soup stock?
Yes.
What should we do with the spinach?
Let's dress it with sesame seeds.
Sakura, egg.
Here.
O Father in Heaven, hallowed be your name, your kingdom come, your will be done on Earth as it is in Heaven. Give us this day our daily bread and forgive us our sins, as we forgive those who sin against us. Lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil, for the kingdom, the power, and the glory are yours, now and forever. Amen.
Feels like it's been a while since we've done this.
Yes.
Not gonna eat?
You don't need to be shy.
We do not need to absorb nutrients like you do.
Really? Saber ate a bunch.
Your customs and I do not mix.
Oh, well, in that case...
So, about our plans moving forward.
I want Sakura to win and use the Holy Grail.
But I think she should stay inside.
It's too dangerous to let her see Zouken face-to-face.
Your opinion is correct.
But how do you plan to defeat that magus?
I think we should work with other Masters.
Who else is left?
Tohsaka and Archer, Sakura and Rider...
Zouken has Assassin...
Other than that, Illya and...
Berserker...
Will you be okay?
Yeah, probably.
Make sure you don't go outside, okay?
Are you regretting this?
After all that's happened, I can't regret anything.
Rider, if it gets too dangerous, bring Senpai home.
But Sakura,
I believe the priest warrants more caution than that old man.
You're right.
I actually think so, too.
But don't worry, Rider.
He can't win against me.
Senpai...
That's it. I just have to make sure he doesn't go outside.
Then he'll never be in danger ever again.
Huh? What am I thinking?
Well, this is a problem.
Am I supposed to follow it?
Huh?
It's gone.
What's it doing here?
You're a cowardly Servant, just like your lord.
Neither of you has the will to fight me.
That's how precious your life is to you.
Yes, indeed it is.
I seek immortality.
Behold my body.
It rots from moment to moment, emits a foul odor, and loses all my accumulated knowledge.
Can you comprehend the pain of rotting alive?
No human exists who does not fear death.
But if it will grant my wish,
I will gladly kill the humans of the world one by one.
I'm floored.
How could you have lost sight of yourself this badly, Makiri?
Remember our precious wish.
Remember what led us to long for a miracle.
Remember why we humans attempted to reach a domain humans cannot tread.
Impressive words, for a mere doll.
Perhaps you've taken imitating your ancestors too much to heart.
Enough of this tomfoolery.
The great Matou Zouken has come to claim the Einzberns' Holy Grail.
No, Berserker!
Tohsaka? Why?
Who would've thought we'd be on the same page?
You've got to be kidding me!
Get away from there!
If that thing gets you, there's no coming back!
And so it's decided.
I leave the rest to you.
Einzbern girl, try not to make your death pitiful.
Berserker!
Illya!
Archer, you...
Berserker...
I'm the one you're gonna be fighting.
Archer.
I'm counting on you.
It's over.
Even the purest of Heroic Spirits cannot resist that mass of curses.
As you are now, you are no different from the vengeful spirits filling this forest.
Berserker!
This is bad.
Berserker...
Berserker!
No...
No!
I have fulfilled my duty.
I leave the rest to you.
You have my gratitude.
Now I can make up for my blunder.
Saber!
Illya!
This is as far as you go.
You are unneeded.
Can't kill one little boy without making a surprise attack?
Pathetic.
How can you be here?
I wonder.
Archer!
Hurry!
If that thing catches up to you, you're done for.
We can talk later. Run, boy!
Now that you've taken Illya's hand, you'd better protect her to the end!
Let's go!
Why?
Why can you move?
Surely you know!
Unlike the others, I am no upstanding hero.
As I am not pure, I can tolerate a certain amount of taint.
I am, myself, a twisted Heroic Spirit!
Good job, Archer!
You can go back to your spirit form now.
Let's hurry on out--
Tohsak--
Huh?
No...
Archer!
Tohsaka!
Get a move on already, you fool!
It's gathering mana.
At this rate...
Tohsaka, run!
I am the bone of my sword.
Steel is my body.
I have created over a thousand blades.
Rho Aias!
Shirou...
Why?
Shirou!
Shirou!!
This is as far as I go.
You did a good job, Tohsaka.
Are you sure about this?
If you do this, you will...
I don't even have to think about it.
If I do nothing, two will disappear.
But if I do this, one will certainly be saved.
I'm home, Sakura.
Oh, right.
Yeah, I guess this is pretty surprising to look at.
I, uh, got a bit of a scratch.
It looks really bad 'cause it's all wrapped up,
but it's nothing big.
Oh, I ran into Tohsaka while I was there.
She helped me, and we've agreed to a bit of a ceasefire.
And this is Illya.
Um, sorry to spring this on you...
Sakura?
Can you move your arm?
No.
I'm not surprised.
It's downright insane to transplant a Servant's body parts onto a human.
Listen up.
If you use that arm even once, Archer's Magic Circuits will activate.
Your body can't withstand that influx of mana,
so it'll collapse from the inside out.
Then this cloth is...
It's a seal.
Thanks, Tohsaka.
Huh? Where'd that come from?
I plan on working with you until we defeat Zouken,
and it's more convenient if I have her nearby.
I see you're thinking about Sakura.
Look, that's not what--
Plus, if I'd never become a Master,
I never would've met you.
That's where you're wrong.
I don't know about you, but I've actually known you for quite a while.
It was four years ago, I think.
You were doing running high jumps until sundown.
I was there.
There was this idiot who kept trying jumps he couldn't do.
And I was watching him like an idiot, too.
I'm the kind of person who'll give up the instant I decide I can't do something.
I'm cold at heart.
But, you know, I'm a magus.
Right when I was wondering if that's what I wanted from my life,
I found someone who was my exact opposite.
It really threw me for a loop.
Don't take them.
Don't take my memories from me.
Ow.
Who knows? Maybe it'll be back to normal if I take the cloth off.
No.
This is not good.
Shirou.
I have a question for you.
Sakura's happiness is for you to live and be with her.
There is nothing else that she wishes for.
I wish for her to survive.
I am quite fond of her.
Shirou, are you on Sakura's side?
No matter what may happen in the future?
Senpai...
Sakura?
Oh, you need mana?
Come in and give me a second.
Let's see, what did I do with my box cutter?
S-Sakura?
Senpai, why do you protect me?
Because...
I wanted you to be with me.
I need you. I couldn't even imagine us being apart.
Do you see me as family?
Or do you see me as a girl?
Yeah. I love you, Sakura.
Then make love to me.
Senpai, am I tainted?
Is there something wrong with me?
Just by coming to your room, I'm already like this.
Even if I try to console myself, I can't suppress it.
I can't think of anything but you.
I'm disgusting.
No. You're not disgusting.
You're beautiful.
Senpai...
I'm horrible.
When Nee-san took you away earlier,
I was so afraid.
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
Senpai...
Sakura...
I love you, Senpai.
It is time for the blessing.
Blessing?
For what?
For the other Holy Grail in the process of being born.
It was birthed by humans as "all the evils of the world,"
and now it carries something humans never wished for in its womb.
The distinction between good and evil.
Rather than try to answer that question,
what if one were to give birth to something that could?
The answer approaches.
Even if this question is blasphemy against God,
I will stand before Him, and with all my soul,
I will even kill the Lord.
If I'm gonna live with you, I'm at least gonna make breakfast.
I'll go help Tohsaka-senpai.
Ah, Sakura.
Yes?
Um, try telling Tohsaka.....
Hmm, what to do?
Nee-san, I'll wash these vegetables.
Yeah, thanks a...
Does it sound weird, Nee-san?
Oh, I wouldn't say /weird/...
Illya, can we talk about you-know-what in my room?
What's you-know-what?
I figure we need a secret weapon or two.
The knowledge of the Einzberns is in Archer's arm.
Tohsaka said we might be able to put it to use somehow.
I don't really care about Kischur Zelretch's leftovers,
but the treasure box of a magician sounds pretty.
Kischur Zel...
Senpai.
Um, thank you.
I only ever watched her from afar,
so I never imagined I'd get to call her Nee-san.
Did you two not hang out after you went to the Matous?
No.
We just knew the fact that we were sisters,
and we tried our best not to come into contact with each other.
And if she knew about my magecraft, she'd hate me.
Hate you? Why?
The Matou family's techniques have always been limited to taking from others.
All they do is steal. They have no teachings for accepting others.
Do you hate the Matous' magecraft?
Sure, their teachings are strict,
but they're nothing compared to what you go through.
I've seen the training you do at night.
I wanted to stop you so many times.
Your training was dangerous.
It was like you were stabbing yourself in the throat.
Nobody forced it on you. You just stubbornly kept up that routine on your own.
I'm sure you're the strongest out of all of us.
Not because of your magecraft, but because you're pure of heart.
I could tell from the moment we met
that you'd never betray anything.
You stole everything from me, Emiya!
Why?
Why won't anything happen?
On to our next headline.
Multiple bodies thought to be homicide victims have been discovered in Fuyuki-shi, Shinto's Central Park.
See, look!
Those weeds have turned black.
Then that means the shadow did it?
Is this Zouken's handiwork?
I don't know. I don't think he'd leave all this evidence behind.