Please give me your pity
awaremi wo kudasai
Touch me the way you would a fallen baby bird
ochita kotori ni sotto fureru you na
And caress me with that same sadness
kanashimi wo kudasai
Let your eyes fill with tears
namidagunde mioroshite
Glance gently down upon me
kawaisou da to kuchi ni dashite
And whisper those sweet words of pity
kutsu no saki de korogashitemo kamawanai wa
I won't mind if you kick me over with your shoes
yogoretetemo ii kara to
Tell me it's okay to be sullied
dorodarake no te wo totte
By holding my mud-covered hand
nee wa ni natte odorimashou
Say, let's form a circle and dance!
mezawari na uzou muzou wa subete
Let's go and eat up
tabete shimaimashou
All of those eyesores
supaisu wa taegatai kurai ga ii wa
Can I add spices until the dish is ruined?
Lie, la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la
The scared little bird
obieta kotori wa
Was unable to speak farewells
sayonara nante ienakute
It falls silent, an act to beg for more love
ai wo kou shigusa from damarikonde
Yet still thinking it's being modest
tsutsumashii tsumori from ita
Lie, lie—It's a lie
Not a lie, it hurts too much
not a lie mou tsurai
Cover me in wounds
sanzan kizutsuite
Anyone would want to live in a gentler world
yasashii sekai ni dare datte yukitai wa
Let us melt into one
hitotsu ni tokete shimaimashou
Let HATE and LOVE get all jumbled up
nikushimi mo aijou mo mushamusha to
And let's stuff our cheeks full with it
hoobatte shimaimashou
Inside this sweet, sweet pot of chaos
konton no amai amai tsubo no naka de
Lie, lie, lie, la la la
La lie, la lie
Lie, la la la la la la la
Lie lie lie, la la la
La la, la la
La la la la la la la
When you flash that uncertain smile
aimai ni warau kara
I want to be with you again
aitai to omou no yo
I know you're here to stay with me
I just want to be loved
aisareteitai dake
Lie, lie, lie, you're to be with me
There, where the thunder blooms
raimei no saku tokoro
A miserable, heavenly feeling
santantaru heavenly feeling
Let love be all that remains
ai dake nokoreba ii
Silently, nothing but sadness keeps snowing down on me
shinshin to kanashimi dake ga furitsumoru
Both wishes and regrets are just being crammed inside me
ganbou mo kaikon mo tada umetsukusu
Even the scars of our fateful spring day
kizuna musunda tooi haru no hi wo
Have fully faded away
kizuato sae mo kieteshimau no
At last, within my sparkling dream
yagate kirakira yume no naka
The dying light
kuchiteyuku hikari wa anata ni
Should one day reach you
todoku hazudakara
My tears won't stop
mabushikute namida ga tomaranai
Say, please be by my side
nee douka soba ni ite
Hold my mud-covered hand
dorodarake you wo not totte
Don't let go
hanasanaide
Please stay by side forver
douka zutto soba ni ite
Don't let go
hanasanaide
It's getting dark
kuraku naru no soba ni ite
Please stay by my side
hanasanaide
I can't see
mienai wa
Don't let go
tada zutto soba ni ite
Just stay by my side forever
hanasanaide
Just forever
tada zutto
I love you
aishiteru