Saber!
Saber...
You're safe.
I made it in—
Saber!
How...
am I here again?
Who are you?
What in the hell...
are you?
On-site investigations are continuing,
but as the police entered the destruction site
this morning... PART OF MT. ENZO COLLAPSED
But as ten police entered
the destruction site this morning...
out as the episode entered' the destruction
s/te this morning... Um, Senpai...
Um, Senpai...
They found some of the temple
buf/d/hgs he I/e collapsed. Um, Senpai. ..
buildings have collapsed.
They found some of the temple
buildings have collapsed. SenpaV?
Senpai?
We'll take you to the scene.
SenpaV?
We 'll fake you f0 the scene.
Y-Yeah, What is it?
I'm here in front of Ryudou Temple,
Oh, it's just...
located at Mt. Enzo
in the Miyama area...
/0cafe0' a!' Ml'. E020 in the Miyama area- - -
Saber left for her home all of a sudden, didn't she?
Saber left for her home
all of a sudden, didn't she?
The sire is cordoned.
- - Saber left for her home all of a sudden, didn't she?
The site is cordoned...
Yeah.
and we are unable to see inside.
The collapse occurred in the building
and the area around the pond.
But now,
you no longer have to so out
at night, right?
So, you're not going to be
in danger anymore, right?
No.
You're wrong about that, Sakura.
I wasn't tagging along with Saber.
Saber was the one
who was tagging along with me.
I might be going out more often now.
But I don't want you to wait for me
at the entrance.
That's right.
It's not over yet.
The one I must fight...
is still in this city.
LANE CLOSED
AT FUYUKI ON-RAMP DUE TO ACCIDENT
ALL LANES NOW CLEAR
New City.
Central Park.
Ryudou Temple.
What is the shadow-like thing after?
And what is its relationship
with Zouken?
Is it working for him?
Or is he just taking advantage of it?
I may have to ask Tohsaka about this.
What the...
You're still alive, Big Brother!
Tell me your name.
Your name, Big Brother.
S-Sure.
I'm Shirou. Shirou Emiya.
Shirou!
Shirou! Shirou! Right?
Yep!
H-Hold on!
Hold on a second!
We're enemies,
aren't we, Illyasviel?
Just call me Ill ya!
Masters can only fight
each other at night.
I came here to chat with you,
Shirou.
Look, you suddenly hacked away at me,
and now you wanna chat with me?
What? That was just an accident!
It was all because you jumped
in recklessly even though you're weak!
I could kill you right here,
right now, too.
Without Saber,
you'd be killed in an instant!
Besides,
I've been waiting for this chance
all this time.
So, don't I deserve a little chat?
So, you're living
in the castle in the forest.
All alone?
No, with Sella and Liz.
I sneaked out behind Sella's back
just to see you!
You should feel honored!
Oh, I guess.
Then, can I ask you one more thing?
Does the name Kiritsugu Emiya
ring any bells?
Ill ya?
Don't know.
I don't know a name like that.
I'm going home.
Ill ya]
Huh?
Emiya?
Tohsaka!
Good timing!
I wanted to have a chat with you, too.
We could chat at school, too, you know.
Archer, can you make us some tea?
You don't want to?
What's with that face?
Jeez, fine!
Huh?
This is...
What are you doing?
Now, let's discuss our game plan.
I have to get ready for dinner.
Why didn't you tell me earlier
that Sakura had a fever?
'Cause you didn't let me interrupt you!
It's open.
Sakura, are you awake?
Emiya?
Jeez!
Shinji! Let go of Sakura!
Shinji!
Don't worry, Sakura.
I won't kill Emiya or anything.
I just want him
to feel a little pain, that's all.
Fight with Rider.
If you survive,
I don't mind letting go of her.
Get him, Rider!
If you were going to fight,
you shouldn't have come alone.
What's wrong, Emiya?
It'd be so boring
if you croaked too easily!
You won since you have
good endurance.
Good! Now, don't hold back anymore.
Just kill him off right now, Rider!
Stop it, Big Brother-
Sakura...
Senpafl
Wh...
Why?
Magecraft...
Rider!
Kill him!
T—Tohsaka?
Why?
Emiya and I have formed a coalition.
It just so happens
that we were together all day today.
Because you used Sakura as bait,
you completely made yourself
my enemy.
Sakura...
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura,
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura!
Why do you care about someone
like her?
I was the one who became a Master!
Stand up, Rider!
Damn you!
Don't...
Rider, please don't...
Stop right now!
— Sakura!
— Emiya, get down!
Gotta be kidding.
This is...
Rider?
Good going, Rider!
Keep at it and get rid of them all!
Hey, Rider!
I see.
Matou's bloodline is already obsolete,
and can't produce anyone
who can handle Magecraft.
I'd thought Zouken was the one
who summoned Rider
and had lent her to Shinji.
But it was actually a lot simpler
than that.
Tohsaka?
In the current state of the Matou family,
the one most fit to become a Master...
...is the rightful heir of Matou,
their current Mage. And that's you,
Sakura.
Sakura...
is a Master?
The transfer of Command Spells...
A Command Spell for Rider
to obey Shinji Matou's orders...
With that, Shinji has become
Rider's Master.
Hey.. -
Meanwhile, you lost
your authority as her Master
and became an ordinary Mage.
Who are you guys looking at?
Because the Matou family is the one
that created Command Spells,
such a trick was possible,
wasn't it, Sakura?
Hey!
Look over here!
We haven't finished yet!
One more time, Sakura!
Give me control over her
one more time!
Why are you acting
so goody-goody after all this?
You have one more Command Spell!
Use that, and...
Shinji, Rider will become free from you
if you don't have Command Spells.
And when that happens, even if
you make a False Attendant's Writings,
it'll quickly be burned up,
and that'll be it for you.
Because you were only controlling her
with borrowed Command Spells,
you were never a Master to begin with.
Shinji...
That's right.
I knew that.
I knew that! I knew that!
I knew that!
I knew all along, from the beginning,
I'd never fit this role!
Since I'm not a Master,
you should do it.
Kill them all in my place, Sakura.
No, Big Brother.
Let's stop it here!
You broke your promise.
You said you wouldn't kill Senpai!
So, please...
Then, fine.
Why don't you just...
die?
Sakura!
Senpai...
No!
Don't look at me!
Sakura...
Looks like she can't control it.
Get away from this place!
If we carelessly feed her
magical energy, we can't revert her!
Please don't get in our way.
Pull back, Rider!
Your master is running out of control!
At this rate, she'll use up
all her magical energy and self-destruct!
It simply means she must take in more
magical energy than she's expending.
So, a change in your master
hasn't changed your rotten nature!
A barrier?
Stop it.
Stop this already, Rider!
I...
didn't summon you because I wanted
to do something like this!
I cannot abide by that command.
I prioritize your life
more than anything else.
No way! Mystic Eyes of Petrification?
Tohsaka!
N000!
Sakuu.
Ra...
Sakura!
Emiya,
are you all right?
Tohsaka!
So, you're finally awake.
I just finished treatment
on Sakura Matou.
How's Sakura?
Is Sakura all right'?
Calm down.
We brought her here with Rider's help.
Kirei, how is Sakura doing?
She's not stable yet,
but her life's been spared for now.
Hold on a second!
What happened
to all of your Magical Crests?
I had no choice but to use them all
for the treatment of Sakura Matou.
All of them?
And the result of that treatment...
Crest Worms?
What the hell are they, um...
Just think of them
as living Magical Circuits.
A Crest Worm,
once it sinks its teeth in,
infiltrates every last inch of your body,
and voraciously devours your spirit.
It pierces through
and lubricates skin with its mucus,
and feeds itself by stimulating
then decomposing the part of the brain
controlling pleasure.
As a result,
women swarmed by these bugs
are completely violated
in both mind and body,
and thus destroyed.
Sakura Matou is also-
Stop it!
I thought you'd need some explanation.
As long as that thing is inside her body,
her magical energy, which is her life
energy, is being sucked away limitlessly.
If you leave her alone,
it will ultimately kill her.
The operation was a success, right?
Not completely.
The worms accumulated for 11 years.
If we forcefully pry them out of her,
she won't last physically.
To completely be rid of them,
that's something you'd actually
have to rely on the Holy Grail for.
Tohsaka?
As the one in charge of Fuyuki,
I'll take care of her.
Take care of her?
You mean Sakura Matou?
Yes. I can't allow Mages
who can't control their powers to live.
She is already nothing
more than a Master gone mad.
Even if...
she is your biological little sister?
Little sister?
The Tohsakas originally had
two children.
But Magecraft is taught
only to one child.
I inherited the Magecraft
of the Tohsakas.
The Matou or Makiri family's bloodline
had already been severed.
So Sakura was adopted by them
as the heir of the family.
Then“.
Sakura and I are sisters by blood.
Though, we've never called
each other as such.
Hold on, Tohsaka!
Then, all the more reason to...
If I leave her alone like this,
the same thing will happen again.
To strangers, next time.
Indiscriminately.
That's why I...
am going to kill her.
You win, Sakura.
So, I'll give you this.
This is the second time...
I've received something important...
from someone dear to me!
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
Sakura...
I've gotta find her before Tohsaka does.
But...
after finding Sakura, what am I...
Good evening, Shirou.
Didn't you say we fight at night?
No. You're no longer a Master.
I know everything, you see.
Rider's Master has also fallen,
so only two more remain.
You want to save Rider's Master,
but you can't find her, right'?
SHUT up!
Shirou, you look like
you're going to cry.
Ill ya, aren't you mad at me?
No, I'm not.
I'm on your side, Shirou.
On my side?
You asked me this morning...
about Kiritsugu... I actually knew him.
The reason I was born
is to win the Holy Grail War,
but my own personal objective
was to kill Kiritsugu and you, Shirou.
But...
if you want to protect
someone dear to you,
I'll be on your side!
It's only natural to protect
the person you're in love with.
I know that!
I've... now lost all places
I can return to!
Sakura...
Sefipai?
Let's go home. You're not fully
over your cold yet, right?
I can't go home.
That thing earlier...
It wasn't a poison or anything.
It's only an elixir
that heightens the senses.
With only some of that,
I lost myself and hurt you!
I'm not hurt at all.
I'm totally okay with something like that.
I am a Mage of the Matou family,
and kept that fact
hidden from you for all this time!
And I didn't tell you
I became a Master, either.
The reason why I was going
to your place so much
was because I was scared
to stand up to Grandfather!
I said I was helping you out,
but I've been fooling you all along!
Always...
I always thought...
I'm not someone
who can stay at your side.
So, I kept thinking
that I'd end all of this today,
and starting tomorrow,
I'd pretend I didn't know you.
That I'd ignore you even if we pass
each other in the campus hallway,
and pretend I didn't know you
after school.
That I'd go home all by myself,
and forget everything
that has happened up until now!
But I couldn't do it!
It was scarier than the moment when I
put a knife to my wrist to commit suicide.
I was scared of deceiving you,
and I was scared of stopping the deceit!
Everything around me was just scary!
I was no longer able to take
even one step forward!
I just didn't know what to do at all!
I wanted to protect my time
together with you going forward, as well.
For me...
For me, that was the only thing...
that means anything to me.
The person I want to protect...
The person who is important to me...
If I don't want that person
to cry anymore...
If nobody is going to reprimand Sakura,
and she has to reprimand herself...
I'll lead her by the hand,
and make sure to take her
to a brighter place.
Even if nobody were to forgive her...
I Will...
continue to forgive you in your place.
So don't cry anymore.
I fully understand now
that you are a bad person.
I don't know when I'll lose sight
of myself again, like I did earlier.
I'm sure I'll do something
that'|| be simply irreparable.
So where are you saying
someone like me can go home to'?!
This is your home, Sakura.
I...
I'm...
not a virgin.
My first time was quite a longtime ago.
That's not all.
Ever since that first time,
my body has been touched
by unnatural things.
I don't deserve to be protected by you!
I will protect you.
No matter what happens,
even if you try to kill yourself,
I'll protect you, Sakura.
Senpai...
I will become a hero of justice
just for you, Sakura!
You can't do that, Senpai.
I'm sure I will end up
hurting you that way!
I will hurt you, yet...
Let's go home.
Sakura...
Big Sis...
Tohsaka-senpai...
Shirou Emiya...
If you kept the belief you've been
sticking with, continue to do so.
The results are obvious.
But if you're going to choose
a different path,
there is no future for Shirou Emiya.
You will end up losing
anything and everything.
You must be tired.
Take your time and rest up.
O-Okay.
What's wrong, Sakura?
Do you have a fever?
You were in the rain for so long.
I—It's not a cold.
My magical energy is a bit...
lacking.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Um...
Would you like to...
No! I'll be fine if you could give me
a small amount of your blood.
S-Sure.
Is this okay?
Yes.
Are you Okay?
I-I see.
Well then, g-good night.
Okay.
I shouldn't go any further!
I can't contaminate him
any more than this!
Sakura, can you make a soup stock?
Okay!
What about the spinach?
Let's dress it with sesame today.
Sakura, eggs.
Here!
— Thank you for the meal!
It's been a while
since we did this last time.
Yes.
You're not gonna eat?
It's okay. Don't be shy.
We Servants don't require the intake of
nutrients the same way you do.
Is that so?
Saber used to eat a lot.
Your way doesn't suit me.
Well then,
if that's the case...
For our strategy from now on...
I will have Sakura win,
and have her use the Holy Grail.
But I think
Sakura had better not go outside.
It'd be dangerous
if she saw Zouken in person.
I believe that idea is correct.
However,
how will you defeat that Mage?
I think we should cooperate
with the other Masters.
Who else is left?
Tohsaka's Archer, Sakura's Rider...
Zouken has his Assassin in tow.
Other than that, I||ya's...
Berserker.
Is it going to be all right?
Yeah, probably.
Don't go outside, okay?
Are you regretting this?
I can't have regrets
after coming this far.
Rider, if things get dangerous,
bring Senpai back home.
But Sakura...
I think the one we should be
careful of is...
that priest instead of the elderly man.
Right.
I actually think so, as well.
But rest assured, Rider.
Because there's no way
he can win against me.
Well then...
Senpafl
I got it! All I have to do
is keep him from going outside.
That way, he won't be
in any danger again, right?
Huh?
What was I just thinking about?
Talk about rough trekking.
Guess it wants me to follow, huh'?
Huh?
It's gone.
What happened to this?
You sure are a cowardly Servant,
much like your master.
I can't feel any intent
to fight against us.
Do you value your life that much?
Of course I do.
My wish is for eternal life.
Look at this body!
With each moment it rots,
emitting a foul odor,
losing the knowledge
I have stashed away within.
Do you understand the pain
of rotting away while you're still alive?
No human is fearless of death.
If that was going to grant me my wish,
I would run around the entire world
killing every human one by one.
I'm disgusted.
You have lost sight
of things that much, Makiri?
Remember again
what we earnestly wished for.
Remember where our thirst
for achieving the miracle came from.
And why we've been striving to reach
the point where we're not human...
while keeping our human bodies.
Quite the words from a mere puppet.
Of course they've
pre-programmed you, huh?
Playtime is now over.
I, Zouken Matou, will take
the Einzberns' Holy Grail.
No, don't, Berserker!
Tohsaka! Why?
I never thought you'd come up
with the same idea, Emiya.
Gotta be kidding me!
Get away from there!
If that thing gets you,
you won't be able to come back!
The score has been settled.
I'll leave you to do the rest.
Don't let the Einzbern girl go
after all this effort.
Berserker!
Ill ya]
Jeez, Archer...
Berserker...
I will be your opponent.
Archer!
I'm counting on you.
This is the end.
A genuine Heroic Spirit...
could not fight
the Cursed Boundary Layer of that thing.
At present, you are not much different
from the phantoms filling this forest.
Berserker!
This doesn't look good.
Berserker...
Berserker!
No...
No!
My duties are complete.
I will leave you to do the rest.
How gracious of you.
I can regain the points I have lost.
Saber!
Ill ya]
That's far enough.
You're of no use.
You can't kill a puny boy
unless you do a sneak attack, can you?
Pathetic.
How could you come here?
Who knows?
Archer!
Hurry!
If that thing catches up, it's all over!
We'll talk later. Run, brat!
Now that you've taken I||ya's hand,
protect her until the very end!
Let's so!
I—low?
How are you able to move?
That's obvious.
I am not a proper Heroic Spirit
like the others.
As I am not canonical,
a little defilement won't affect me.
Which means that I am also
a distorted Heroic Spirit!
Good job, Archer!
You can return to spirit form now.
We have to hurry up and get out-
Tohsak—
No...
Archer!
Tohsaka!
Hurry up and get out of here, fool!
Magical energy is gathering!
If this keeps going...
Run, Tohsaka!
I am the bone of my sword.
Steel is my body.
I have created over a thousand blades.
Rho Aias!
Shirou...
Why?
Shirou!
Shirou!!
I guess this is it for me.
Take care, Tohsaka.
Are you insane?
If you did such a thing, you would...
Not even worth a thought.
If I do nothing, two will be dead.
But this way, at least
one will definitely be saved.
I'm home, Sakura.
Oh, right.
Of course you're surprised
that I look like this.
Yeah, I got slightly injured.
It looks terrible
because it's bandaged so heavily,
but it's really not that big a deal.
I saw Tohsaka while I was out.
She helped me out,
and we have a cease-fire for now.
And this is Ill ya.
Sorry to be so sudden, but...
Sakura?
Can you move your arm?
No.
Thought so.
Transplanting a body part of a Servant
onto a human is unheard—of.
Listen.
If you use that arm even once,
Archer's Magical Circuits will activate.
And your body won't be able to
withstand the power from them,
and you'll collapse from the inside.
Then, this cloth is...
It's a seal.
Tohsaka, thank you.
Wh—What's this so suddenly?
I'm going to work with you
until we defeat Zouken.
And besides, it's convenient for me
to stay close to her.
You're concerned about Sakura.
I'm telling you, that's...
Besides, if I didn't become
a Master myself,
I'd never have gotten
to know you like this.
That's a little different
from what you think.
I don't know about you,
but I've known about you
for quite a while now.
I think it was about four years ago.
You were doing the high jump
over and over until sunset, weren't you?
I happened to be there.
There was an idiot who kept jumping
even though it was obvious
he couldn't do it.
And I was watching him like an idiot.
I usually back off from things
if I find them impossible for me to do.
I'm cold through and through.
But you know, I'm a Mage after all.
So, I was about to compromise, like,
"Oh, well, my life can be fine as it is now."
But that was just when I saw someone
who was my polar opposite.
I was pretty shocked, you know?
Don't take it away from me.
Don't take that memory away from me
along with other things!
Ow.
What if I take this cloth off?
My arm might be back to normal, huh?
No...
This is...
no good.
Shirou...
There is something I'd like to ask you.
Sakura's happiness is to have you
stay alive and stay by her side.
She wishes nothing else.
I'm wishing for her survival.
I am rather fond of her.
Shirou, do you side with Sakura?
Will you, no matter what happens
in times to come?
Senpai...
Sakura?
Oh, you're low on magical energy, huh?
You can step inside and wait for me.
Let's see. Where did I put
that cutter-knife'?
S-Sakura?
Senpai, why are you protecting me?
It's because...
I'm the one who wants you by my side.
I need you,
and I don't think
we could stay far from each other.
Do you mean you like me
as one of your family members?
Or...
as a girl?
Yeah. I love you, Sakura.
Then,
please make love to me.
Senpai, am I impure?
It's so strange.
I end up like this
just by coming into your room.
I try to quench it by myself,
but it just won't subside.
I can't think of anything
other than you, Senpai!
I'm such a defiled...
No.
You're not defiled at all.
You're beautiful, Sakura.
Senpai...
I...
can't take it.
When Big Sister...
took you out earlier,
I became terribly frightened just by that!
I'm sorry I didn't notice.
Senpai...
Sakura...
I love you, Senpai.
Time for a blessing.
Blessing?
For what?
For the other Holy Grail
that is about to be born.
And it has conceived
all the evil in this world
that was born from people,
yet never been wanted by them.
The whereabouts of good and evil.
If it gives birth to something
that can answer
instead of answering the question itself,
what do you think would happen?
The answer is near.
And what if this question
blasphemes against God?
Then, in front of God,
I would give every bit of myself,
and I shall question
even my Lord until death.
Since you let me stay here,
I'll at least make breakfast for all.
I'll go help Tohsaka-senpai.
Oh, Sakura...
YES?
You know, for Tohsaka...
Now, what to do...
Big Sister, I'll wash
the vegetables over here.
Yes, please do...
Is it strange after all,
Big Sister?
Th-Th-Th-There's nothing strange
about that!
Ill ya, about that thing...
Can we do it in my room?
What is "that thing"?
I thought we'd need one or two
secret weapons up our sleeve.
Archer's arm contains knowledge
of the Einzberns, you know?
I suggested to Tohsaka that there might be
something to make good use of it.
I have no interest
in what Kischur Zelretch left behind,
but a treasure box
that he left may be pretty.
Kischur Zel...?
Senpai...
Um...
Thank you very much.
I'd always just watched her from afar.
I never thought that a day would come
when I could call her "Big Sister."
You had no interaction with Tohsaka after
you were adopted into the Matou family?
No.
Both Big Sister and I merely knew
we were sisters as a fact.
We both tried our best
not to interact with each other.
Besides, if she found out
what kind of Magecraft I use,
I'm sure she'll hate me.
Hate you? Why would that be?
Every single Matou's Magecraft technique
is to pillage from others to start with.
All we do is pillage, and there's no skill
to be taught to give back to others.
Sakura, do you dislike
the Magecraft of the Matou family?
Their teachings were indeed strict,
but it's nothing compared to you, Senpai.
I once saw you training so hard at night.
I felt so many times
that I had to stop you.
Your training was a very dangerous one.
It was...
as if you were piercing
through your own throat.
Even though no one forced you to do so,
you stubbornly kept at it
for the longest time all by yourself.
I'm sure that among us,
you are the strongest one.
Not because of any Magecraft affixes,
but because the very nature
of your heart is so pure.
I've known since the day we first met...
that you would never betray anyone.
You took her from me, Emiya!
Why won't...
anything happen?
MULTIPLE CORPSES
IN NEW CITY CENTRAL PARK
MULTIPLE CORPSES IN NEW CITY CENTRAL
PARK And now, our next news story. ..
MULTIPLE CORPSES
IN NEW CITY CENTRAL PARK
MULTIPLE CORPSES IN NEW CITY CENTRAL
PARK A body Wes found, presumably murdered,
at Central Park
in the New City district of Fuyuki.
A! Cenfra/ Park in fhe New C/zj/
d/sfr/cf of Fuyuk/I See? Right here!
There were four victims,
There Were four v/cl/ms,
The weeds have turned black!
And they are currently /n vesf/gal/hg on their
causes of deaf iv. .. The weeds have turned black!
And they are currently investigating
on their causes of death...
That means that Zouken had
the shadow do this?
I don't know about that.
I don't think he'd leave behind
evidence like this.
Next up is tomorrow's weather.
Miss Sato
from the weather forecasting center?
Yes. Here's the weather-
Huh?
I don't taste anything.
So warm...
It's fine. I can still feel this.
I wish this moment would continue forever.
Walking along, flip-flop.
An empty head sways to and fro.
Vacating all the nitty-gritty objectives.
Trembling, shimmy-shimmy and a go-go.
Singing, tee-bee and a 30-30.
Dried-out limbs, just like paper balloons,
roll around the ground, tumble-tumble.
Huff-puff, floating and flying
is when you become an adult.
Go-go.
Someone is coming by, squeak-squeak.
A laughter, cackle—cackle—cackle—cackle.
I don't remember fascinating you at all!
Because they echo so loudly,
scritch —scratch...
the tummy started to rumble-grumble.
You're working hard, aren't you?
That's why I told you to die
before it's too late.
Twinkle-twinkle...
So beautiful...
The grace period is now over.
This is my mercy to you.
What? You're still breathing?
I wasn't expecting your body,
not just the shadow,
to be in the transformation phase.
To think you'd attempt to make me kneel!
Damn you!
Surely you haven't gone that far!
Did you see that?
Huh?
Shirou!
Come to the living room right away!
Around 22-'30 tonight,
IN FRONT OF THE NEW CITY STATION there Was a
Widespread blackout near the New C/ty Station.
IN FRONT OF THE NEW CITY STATION
There are also multiple
incomprehensible reports to the police...
about neighbors disappearing,
people gone missing
or people suddenly vanishing.
Sakura!
Hold on! I'll get med!
Saku-
Don't notice.
Stop!
Don't think that it looks like her!
Over 60 victims
have already been confirmed.
The residents of roughly 40 buildings
are unaccounted for.
How is Sakura?
She's alive.
However...
Something wrong?
Sakura's body is just connected
to look fine on the outside.
The muscles in her arms and legs
are completely tattered.
I'm positive that she died
at some point for sure.
I don't know who got her.
But the pain may have destroyed
not only her body, but her brain, as well.
We have to defeat Zouken
and that shadow as quickly as we can.
Let's do everything in our power to do that.
But Shirou...
What if Zouken and that black shadow
are completely different things?
What will you do then?
Good morning.
Do you still have
a sense of yourself left, Sakura?
Where in the world
did you take in a soul like that?
Assassin and Rider are still around,
but you're sufficiently satisfied?
This is a surprise.
Sakura, do you know
what's going to happen to you?
I don't.
What's going to happen to me?
You'll die.
You can't be saved no matter what.
I'm home!
I made it back at least a little bit!
Wait, Shirou, you're not home?
Who's that?
Jeez!
Where did Shirou go?
When Sakura is very sick!
Oh, you shouldn't! Don't get up.
Senpai said...
he was going to protect me.
However...
I'm sorry,
because of me,
his dreams will be shattered!
How so?
Because“.
I'm a bad person.
Shirou can properly scold you and tell you
that you shouldn't do bad things.
Sakura, you want to fix all the bad things
about you, too, don't you?
Yes.
Then no worries.
Besides, Shirou's dream
is to be a hero of justice, right'?
Of course he has someone
he wants to protect!
But that means
he'd protect everyone equally.
If Shirou is aiming
to become like Kiritsugu,
it's totally all right for him
to have someone special.
Kiritsugu played favorites, too, you know!
Even after he started living in this city,
Kiritsugu went overseas
over and over again.
All the way until he could
no longer move his body.
I'm sure there was someone
he desperately wanted to see.
It's a very painful thing to not be able
to see someone you really care about.
Even for a hero of justice.
That's why...
Sakura, please stay by Shirou's side.
Are you going to betray?
Are you going to betray
who you used to be?
Hey.. -
Stop it!
If your answer is "yes ..
You are...
Stop it!
No way!
That just can't be!
Shirou Emiya...
Is that right?
My Lord Mage
would like to speak with you.
Well, you arrived earlier than I thought,
Emiya's boy.
Zouken...
There is only one thing I will say!
Release Sakura immediately!
Release, huh?
I guess you could put it that way.
Shirou Emiya,
I called you here today
because I wish to ask you for a favor.
I'd like you to kill that shadow.
Isn't that thing one of your allies?
An ally?
As if I could communicate with that thing.
I can't even calm it down
since last night.
Oh, before all that, I should tell you
what exactly that shadow is.
Bluntly put, that thing
is the content of the Holy Grail.
The "will" that is overflowing
from the gate called the "Holy Grail."
That's what that shadow is.
The shadow...
and the gate...
I asked you to kill the shadow,
but that will be a difficult task.
However,
you're still able to kill the gate.
It will catch on if it were to be
me or Tohsaka's girl.
Servants would be
nothing more than its feed.
Stop it!
The only one who can implant
a piece of the Holy Grail in it,
and kill the "Holy Grail of Matou"
that I nurtured for the last ten years-
Stop!!
You have been aware, haven't you...
that it resembles Sakura?
The doll that doesn't do anything
but exists here...
will come to an end
by the hands of its beloved man.
Surely it will be the happiest.
We have no time left.
Once Sakura's conscience is gone,
the Holy Grail that has been residing
in her unconscious will surface.
And the catastrophe of ten years ago
will be replicated.
If you want to save Sakura,
you must persevere until the time limit
for the Holy Grail War is reached.
Judging from past examples,
that should be about four more days' time.
Thoughts?
Do you think Sakura will last that long?
She will! Of course she will!
But other people may not last that long.
It may be full now
from the gorging last night,
but it will be on the move again
as soon as tomorrow.
How many more days will it be
before every human in this city
has been devoured?
You surely understand?
Vanquishing evil to save everyone else.
If you would like to succeed
Kiritsugu Emiya,
no one but Sakura Matou...
is your true enemy.
Sakura, are you awake?
Yes.
Good morning, Senpai.
Sakura,
is there anything Wu wanna do
after this battle is over?
I can't really think of anything.
I think I'll be all right...
if I could just be together with you.
Then, let's go out together
somewhere and play.
Where would you like to go?
I'd like to go to the cherry-blossom
viewing party.
All right.
That's a promise.
Having a warm dream
while the heart is frozen...
Someday, winter will pass,
and when the new spring arrives,
we will go...
see the cherry blossoms together.
R/ghf.
When spring arrives...
Senpau
I'm Sakura Matou.
This is the second time...
I've received something important
from someone...
I wanted to protect my time
together with you going forward, as well.
Senpai...
Are you going to betray?
Yeah.
I'm going to betray.
Thank you so much, Senpai.
You've given me so many things.
Thank you, Big Sister.
I was really happy
that I could call you "Big Sister"!
Miss Fujimura, thank you very much.
I'm sorry I couldn't keep
my promise to you.
Rider,
thank you for not killing Senpai.
Sakura...
This is the final Command Spell!
Please, Rider.
I will stop Grandfather.
It's already too late,
but I can't cause any more trouble
than I already have.
Sakura, good morning-
Hey, traitor.
You came home pretty late, didn't you?
U-Um...
Big Brother, I-
Hold this thing for a sec.
It's nothing dangerous.
So beautiful.
You're amazing, Sakura.
Maybe you'll surpass
even Tohsaka someday, huh'?
Big Brother?
Don't get cocky.
After all, you're nothing but my puppet.
I made another mistake.
That's why he's going to do
cruel things to me.
It's fine.
I just have to put up with it
for a while like usual.
Put up with it, put up with it,
put up with it, put up with it...
Sakura...
No!
I don't want to!
I belong to Senpai now!
What's this?
He's tamed you quite a bit, hasn't he?
No!
Hey! Why don't you scream
like usual, huh?
Hey! Why don't you scream like usual, huh?
Why 0'0 I/v/ngs a/Ways end up I/v/s Way?
Hey! Why don't you scream
like usual, huh?
Hey!
I've been thinking for such a long time.
I've harbored hatred for such a long time.
Why does the world around me...
hate me...
this much?
I'll have to tell Emiya about all this.
About how much you begged me...
and how obscene
our intercourses have been!
I wish someone like this didn't exist.
Big Brother...
Sakura!
NEXT CHAPTER PREVIEW
I told you, didn't I?
NEXT CHAPTER PREVIEW That I would become
a hero of justice just for you, Sakura!
So,
grit your teeth!
FINAL CHAPTER
Scheduled for Release in Spring 2020