as if to forbid me from retaining them.
Whenever I dream, this is the endpoint I always reach.
So I'm about to wake up.
Senpai.
Good morning.
Morning, Sakura.
You know, Sakura, you really don't have to come over every single day.
You have your own life to attend to.
It's all right. Cooking and archery are my only hobbies.
And one of my goals for the future is to cook better food than you.
I think it's just about within reach.
Yeah?
You saying you've been learning my secrets?
Absolutely. I hope you're ready.
Also, I just can't find food delicious anymore unless I eat it at your house.
Come on, we'd better hurry if you want to make it to morning practice.
Emiya, are you going out with Matou's sister?
Huh?
You see, I saw you enjoying yourselves on your way to school together.
Come on, she's my friend's sister.
Get real.
Heck, if you saw me, you should've said something.
Unfortunately, I am still in training.
Such a daring move is far beyond me.
Whatever.
Anyway, I'm done with this one.
Morning, Shinji.
Hey, Emiya.
Starting the day off by sticking your nose where it doesn't belong?
You're a weird one, I'll give you that.
Well, I've got nothing better to do.
If you ever need help with something, just say the word.
You've always had a hard time stringing and fixing bows, right?
Say, Emiya, you're through with the archery club, right?
Don't you think it'd be in your best interests to mind your own business?
First off, pronunciation.
Even though the spelling's the same...
Emiya, wanna have lunch?
Sorry. I'm going to the cafeteria today.
Oh, Sakura—
Sakura.
Senpai!
Who was that?
Oh, she's a second-year. Her name is Tohsaka—
Tohsaka, right? Tohsaka Rin.
Do you know her, Senpai?
Well, you know, she's kinda famous.
She always stands out.
Yes, you're right.
Tohsaka-senpai's so pretty, so gallant...
Sakura?
Senpai, are you ever going to come back to the archery club?
I dunno.
I don't think Shinji would like that.
I think my brother doesn't like you.
But he still likes you much more than anyone else.
He's dishonest at heart, so if he hates you, that means he actually likes you.
That's one heck of a personality.
Good night, Senpai.
Do I hear bugs?
But it's winter right now.
Well.
I hear you've done a great deal for my granddaughter.
Um, I'm sorry! My name's Emiya Shirou.
I'm in Shinji's class.
Emiya...
Is the daughter of the Einzberns in good health?
Huh?
This dream again.
Right after this, Kiritsugu saved me.
You'd better summon yours soon,
or you'll die, Onii-chan.
On to our next headline.
Late last night, there was a large-scale gas leak in the office district of Shinto.
Done.
Sakura, can you get me a plate?
Sure.
What's the matter?
Sakura, you sure you're okay? You didn't even have one bite.
You can skip morning practice if you want.
Even the club advisor says it's okay.
No, I'm fine.
Senpai, I have a favor to ask of you.
Could you please try to come home from school as early as possible today?
This just in.
In the residential district of Fuyuki-shi, Miyama-cho,
four individuals were discovered dead in their home.
According to a press release from the Fuyuki police department,
the victims were all killed by some sort of blade. The police are...
Emiya. Emiya.
Emiya!
Morning, Emiya.
Morning, Mitsuzuri.
Emiya, do you know about the murder incident that occurred last night in Miyama-cho?
Murder?
Have they caught the guy?
No, not yet.
I suppose we'll have to suspend after-school club activities.
Excuse me.
Ryuudou, can I borrow you?
Oh, sure.
Sorry, Emiya. We can continue this conversation later.
Well, if it isn't Emiya.
This is a first-year classroom.
What're you doing here?
Shinji...
I thought you didn't have club today.
Club or no club, I'm a busy man. I've got things to do.
Hey, why don't you—
Try not to give Mitsuzuri too much trouble, okay?
What do you mean by that?
I don't want to hear it from an outsider.
That reminds me, Emiya!
Mind doing me a solid?
Sure. What is it?
Just some dumb cleaning up after the dumb archery club.
Isn't that supposed to be your job?
I've got things to do, remember?
But you don't, right?
Help a guy out.
Emiya.
Okay. I don't mind.
That a fact?
Have fun, Mister Goody Two-Shoes.
After-school club activities have been suspended for today.
All faculty and students are to leave school by six PM.
Come on, let's go home.
Okay!
See you later!
See ya!
Hey, let's go in that place!
Yeah, I've been curious about it!
I guess I got a little too into it.
Yeah, let's go home.
What the heck?
Who's there?!
What the heck /is/ that?
Gotta get away.
If I don't, I'll die!
Hey.
Pitiful. This summoning was far too incomplete, far too sloppy.
Though the actors have gathered, their places and their stage are yet unarranged.
This Holy Grail War is a far cry from the grand ritual we sought.
But once it has begun, it cannot be stopped.
If water fills a chalice, someone must drink it.
Fortunately, the supervisor from the Church is none other than that man.
He will mediate this twisted Holy Grail War well.
The Grail summons Heroic Spirits, and the Heroic Spirits require contractors.
If one is swept up into this ritual, their fate is to kill or be killed.
There need only be one left alive.
The seventh Servant to be summoned was that Saber.
And her Master is the son of Emiya.
Truly, fate must be at work.
The Church is a neutral zone. I cannot move against him.
Now, will that man be a saint worthy of preaching the gospel, or will he not he not?
Coming, Emiya-kun?
I don't know why a third-rate magus like you got chosen as a Master,
but the man you're about to meet will explain the Holy Grail War to you.
Careful, he's a creep.
You continue to reject my repeated summons,
but I see you've brought quite the odd guest.
Is he the seventh?
My name is Kotomine Kirei. I have been entrusted with this church.
Emiya Shirou?
Am I correct in assuming that you are Saber's Master?
Saber did save me, yes.
But if you have to be a real magus to be a Master,
you should pick someone else.
Pick a new Master?
Interesting.
Then do you have no interest in the events of ten years ago?
The Holy Grail holds omnipotent power in the world of magi.
It is a vessel that can grant any wish at all.
The chosen Masters fought and killed each other to obtain it.
As a result, an unfortunate accident occurred.
An accident large enough to be called a disaster.
Are you telling me that was...
Yes. It is an event any resident of this city would know.
Five hundred casualties, one hundred and thirty-four buildings burned to the ground.
That raging inferno of cause yet unknown
is a scar caused by the Holy Grail War.
Emiya-kun!
Kirei, I told you to explain the rules to him!
I never asked you to reopen his wounds!
Is this Holy Grail for real?
Last time, there was a man who obtained the Holy Grail, albeit temporarily.
What happened to him?
Nothing. That Holy Grail had not achieved completion.
The Holy Grail will not avail itself to a man who avoids combat..
You sound like you saw it yourself.
I did.
Last time, I participated as a Master and fought for the Holy Grail.
Wait, really?
I fought until partway through the war.
However, I made a crucial mistake in judgment.
As a result, I merely obtained an empty Grail.
What do you me—
Our conversation was only just beginning,
but it seems we have a rather impatient guest.
Say, do you know of the Einzberns?
Now, young man, you are out of time.
Let me hear your answer.
Emiya-kun!
If the Holy Grail War really was the cause of the disaster ten years ago,
I'll...
fight.
I'll fight as a Master!
Rejoice, young man.
Your wish will finally come true.
Every superhero needs a villain to defeat.
Well, I suppose a Servant would never remember.
Are you done talking?
Good evening, Onii-chan. I'm Illya.
Illyasviel von Einzbern.
Thanks for the introduction.
Okay, time to kill you.
Get them, Berserker.
Saber!
Run.
Just run!
Of all the times to not have Archer!
That's the spirit, Berserker!
She regenerates, so lop off her head and have your way with her!
I'm an idiot.
Hey!
No way.
Why?
This is boring.
Master!
God, what is /wrong/ with you?
When I was a kid, I wanted to be a superhero.
But being a hero has a time limit. Once you're an adult, it gets harder to call yourself one.
Kiritsugu...
And taking someone's side means not taking someone else's.
What do I have to do to be a superhero?
Huh?
I'm healed...
Master.
Are you all right?
You awake now?
Tohsaka...
Did you do this?
No, you healed those wounds by your own power.
No way. I can't do something as crazy as that.
Then maybe your contract with Saber is affecting something.
First of all, let's hear your excuse for that stunt you pulled.
I didn't really do anything wrong.
It just didn't go as well as...
We Servants live on the mana provided by our Masters.
If that mana source disappears, we cannot remain here.
Oh, I didn't know.
Well, now you do.
Anyway, I'm gonna get going.
I need to start treating my own Servant.
Oh, and next time we meet, we're enemies.
She's a good person.
What about your injuries, Saber? Are you okay?
Yes, though I'd hesitate to say I'm in perfect condition.
Um, do you want the Holy Grail, too?
Yes. It is the reason I'm here.
Berserker's Master called herself "Einzbern."
Didn't think a little kid like her would be in this.
Saber?
There is someone employing magecraft nearby.
I do not sense Berserker.
This is someone completely different.
Master, your orders?
Let's go.
Be on your guard. A bounded field has been erected.
Where have I felt this before?
Mitsuzuri?
Mitsuzuri!
Now this is a surprise.
Who would've thought you'd be here, Emiya?
Why?
Oh, right.
We had the president of the archery club help us out a little.
Shinji?
What's that, your Servant?
Allow me to introduce you. This is my Servant.
Let's have 'em fight, Emiya.
I've always wanted to see a fight between two Servants.
Shinji, why are you a Master?
The Matous are an old but noble lineage of magi.
As far as they Holy Grail War ar goes, they're one of the three great families.
I wish I didn't have to tell a amateur like you.
As the first-born son of the family...
don't you think it's only right that I join this Holy Grail War?
Shinji!
I see you're just as thick in the head as always!
You've figured it out, haven't you?
This is a game we're all playing for keeps!
Go, Rider!
Huh?
Uh...
Hey.
Who told you you could lose, huh?
Stand up.
Stand up!
You're making it look like I'm weaker than him, dammit!
What? Why?
Dammit!
Go out! Go out!
Go—
Shinji!
It seems the burden was too much for you to bear, Shinji.
This is as far as the Matous go.
What a shame, indeed.
You're...
Grandfather! Wait!
I'm a magus of the Matou family! I'll...
Once incompetent, always incompetent.
The Matou bloodline has fallen from its former glory.
There is absolutely nothing I expect out of you.
Out of him?
Wait! Hold on!
You're not making Sakura do this stuff, are you?!
Why are you bringing up her name, huh?
I'm all we need.
That piece of trash doesn't know the first thing about magecraft!
The teachings of the Matous are mine, and mine alone!
Mitsuzuri!
She is a victim of the Holy Grail War,
so the proper course of action would be to leave her with the supervisor.
Honestly, never did I expect you to return in a matter of hours.
Interesting.
You seem to have caught the eye of something quite nasty.
Huh?
I will be taking care of her now.
So you stayed.
How's Mitsuzuri?
I have finished treating her.
You have nothing to worry about.
In fact, you appear to be much worse off than she is.
I'm all healed up now.
In the War ten years ago, there was a man who stood against me
despite suffering lethal wounds, like yourself.
He was the man who fought me at the end, as well as the man who would become the winner of the previous Holy Grail War.
His name was Emiya Kiritsugu.
Saber.
Mitsuzuri's gonna be okay,
That is a relief.
You seemed to be having quite the long conversation.
Yeah...
He asked me about Kiritsugu. My father.
Master,
there is something I must tell you.
In a word, the man known as Emiya Kiritsugu was a hitman.
He made it his livelihood to exclusvely kill magi.
All magi are unbound by the ethics of the world at large,
but even among them, he was a wonder.
Last time, I was called to this time period and fought as the Einzberns' Servant.
My Master's name at the time was Emiya Kiritsugu.
But...
He truly never did shed blood or tears.
He would consider any method fair game to acheive his goals.
Even face-to-face with an opponent begging for his life, he eliminated him.
In the midst of the war, Kiritsugu considered that priest his greatest enemy.
A fittling descriptor for us.
We had no other option but to kill each other.
He and I fought in the Holy Grail War and survived to the end.
Emiya Kiritsugu betrayed the Holy Grail at the very end.
He destroyed the Holy Grail.
Kill the one to save the ten.
He was an irredeemable saint.
I still don't think the Kiritsugu I know would abandon victims of the Holy Grail War.
I've always looked up to superheroes like that.
So that's why I'm fighting.
I should've said this sooner, but Saber, I want us to fight together.
Regardless of my past, the Command Spells bind me to my Master.
If you want, you can call me Shirou.
Then Shirou it is.
Yes, I do prefer this pronunciation.
Thanks.
Ready to head home?
Yes.
Wow, you knew Kiritsugu-san?
It's too bad your luggage didn't get here...
Sorry you have to use Shirou's hand-me-downs, Saber-chan.
Oh, it's no trouble at all.
Kiritsugu-san's so mean.
I know he traveled abroad a lot, but still.
Do you have any stories about him?
Sorry I sprung this on you out of nowhere, Sakura.
I don't mind.
So, um...
Did you see Shinji this morning?
Yes. Do you need something?
Nah, if nothing happened, it's all good.
Sakura.
Um, Senpail...
Sakura, this bruise...
Was it Shinji?
Emiya-kun.
You've got balls, coming to school without your Servant.
You think I'm not a threat?
Let's make a deal, Tohsaka! I need your help!
Huh?
Uh, huh?
Let's see... Shinji's a Master, Ayako got attacked, and Rider disappeared...
So what? That's not all, is it?
Shinji has a sister. Her name is Sakura.
What about her?
Sakura might get caught up in this. I don't think Shinji's given up.
At this rate...
Then you should probably keep her safe at your place.
At least, if she's really that important to you.
Sakura.
Breakfast this morning was sublime.
And now you're even preparing lunch.
You have my thanks.
Huh?
Um, it's nothing...
Also, if there's anything I can do to help, please say so.
Huh?
Um...
Fight!
Well, in that case...
I'm home!
I figured we'd need a lot.
Saber, this is for you.
Your, uh, luggage came in.
Oh, that's cute!
Man, I owe Tohsaka big-time.
Senpai,
I realize you need things for daily life,
but this seems like quite a lot.
Oh, yeah.
Fuji-nee, I wanna have Sakura stay over here for a little while.
Where'd that come from, Shirou?
It's pretty dangerous around town nowadays.
Plus, Shinji's been too busy to go home.
Sakura?
Um...
That's right!
I have to go get Saber-san's room ready.
Ow!
I'll go, too.
Not gonna stop Saber-chan?
You afraid Sakura-chan's gonna get the wrong idea?
What makes you think that?
Get a load of this.
I hear Sakura-chan's an E cup!
What are you talking about?
Shirou, Sakura collapsed!
Senpai?
I'm sorry.
Guess my idea's paying off already.
I'll stay here a little longer.
I'll keep an eye on you for another half an hour, so get some rest.
Yes.
Thank you for watching me.
Senpai.
Hmm?
About what you said earlier...
Why are you letting me stay here?
Are you worried about me?
Yeah, I am.
So I'd really like it if you stayed here.
Um, I'll take you up on that.
Yeah.
Narily did I expect such manner of serpent...
Is something the matter, Souichirou?
Stay here with everyone.
Assassin, come out.
Assassin!
Souichirou-sama...
What is this man?
First, I cut its neck.
Arms, legs, all cut.
I rent its stomach.
But it moved.
So you're the real Assassin, are you?
You will release me, witch.
Are you happy now?
Emiya-kun.
It's all right.
You have my consent.
You can have your way with me.
Tohsaka...
Um, Senpai...
Come on, what am I thinking?
Sa—
Hello?
Oh, Fuji-nee.
You can't come today?
Okay.
I went to Ryuudou Temple last night.
The mana from the coma incidents in Shinto was flowing back there.
Archer's all healed up, so I thought I'd investigate.
Long story short, Caster was making Ryuudou Temple her base.
But by the time I got there, someone had already taken care of her.
The residents of the temple had their mana stolen, and now they're comatose.
And since Kuzuki-sensei was the only one who got killed,
he was probably Caster's Master.
Now, here's the real problem.
There was another coma incident in Shinto this morning.
Even though Caster's gone?
Sakura ended up staying with you, right?
Huh? Yeah.
She's been at my place since yesterday.
Wanna team up, Emiya-kun?
Everything's turning out different this time from what my father told me.
So before anything else, I wanna figure out what's going on.
You want a temporary alliance?
Yep, that's it.
Rin.
I fail to see the meaning in joining up with a powerless Master.
What was that?
Am I wrong?
Archer, you'd better do as your Master says.
Let's hit the ground running.
Can you go outside tonight?
You formed an alliance with Archer's Master?
Yeah.
Sorry to spring it on you out of nowhere.
It's fine.
Besides, the sooner we end the Holy Grail War,
the sooner Sakura can go back to her normal life.
Shirou, I believe Sakura is in rather poor health.
Oh, no, perhaps I'm overthinking it.
Sakura, is someone here?
What is it, Emiya?
I'm Sakura's brother.
What's wrong with me coming to bring my adorable sister home?
What kind of brother hits his sister?
After what you did to Mitsuzuri, I can't trust you to keep Sakura safe.
Oh, I get it now.
If you're coming after me like this already, that must mean
you don't wanna let her go 'cause you haven't had enough of her yet, huh?
Screw you!
Senpai!
Shinji!
Nice face.
Come at me. Let's pick up where we left off.
Stop it, Nii-san!
Sakura...
I'll do whatever you say.
Just don't do this in front of Senpai!
Sakura, don't you dare forget what you just said.
Senpai, I'm sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for.
No good. I can't focus.
Senpai? Are you there?
Sakura?
Um...
Can we talk for a little bit?
Sure...
Um, I'm sorry for how my brother acted.
I told you, it's not your fault.
It's pretty cold, huh?
Gimme a sec.
Sakura.
It's so warm.
You fixed it?
Yeah.
Took a lot out of me, though.
Senpai, do you remember?
This happened a long time ago.
Back before I met you.
It was a bright red sunset.
The schoolyard, the hallways, everything was red.
It was pretty, but also lonely.
Around then, I saw someone doing running long jumps in the schoolyard.
Back then, I wasn't a very good person.
I watched him and kept hoping he'd mess up.
But...
No matter how many times he tried, he never made the jump,
and eventually he realized he couldn't do it, so he cleaned up and went home.
Uh, Sakura...
Are you saying, uh...
Yes. He was the upperclassman sitting next to me right now.
That's how long I knew about you.
Oh. That's news to me.
Um, Senpai.
Can I ask you a difficult question?
I heard this from Fujimura-sensei, but were you really adopted into this family?
Yeah, I am.
Does that not bother you?
It took some time to get used to, but it's nothing worth losing sleep over.
You must have been surrounded by kind people.
In my case, the people older than me were all pretty unreliable.
Kiritsugu sucked at housework, and you know how Fuji-nee is.
I started doing the chores and just kinda fell into a groove.
I just wanted to be like Kiritsugu.
Like a superhero?
Huh? That's weird.
Senpai, I have another question.
If I ever did something bad, would you forgive me?
No. If you do something bad, I'll get mad at you.
I'll be first in line to yell at you.
Thank you.
That would make me happy.
I'll go to sleep now.
Good night, Senpai.
Miyama HQ to Miyama ambulances.
This just in from the front.
Okay, screw it, this shit's too faint. We'll have to reference other subs.
Hey.
That your handiwork?
Nah, maybe that's too hard for a filthy sand worm like you.
You're not going anywhere.
To me!
That's not gonna work.
I was born this way. Projectiles don't work on me.
The blessing of stray arrows, I see.
You paint your weapons black to hide them in the darkness.
Ridiculous.
You have seen beneath my mask, Lancer!
And I'm just getting started.
This is where you lead me?
What's a sand worm want from a watering hole, huh?
If you do not move, you will be consumed.
You know what this thing is?
Noble Phantasm...
Zabaniya!
Noble Phantasm!
It's a bit early, but this ends here!
Gae...
Bolg!
You have lost this battle!
Well, this couldn't have gone worse.
Senpai...
Tohsaka.
We can talk on the way.
Also, we're being watched, so be careful.
Can I assume that was your doing,
elder of the Matou family?
Impressive, daughter of Tohsaka.
What an exemplary magus you are.
Zouken!
I thought the Matous were out of the game!
Not once did I say I myself had lost.
Archer!
You fiend...
You would make a mockery of a Heroic Spirit's corpse?
How dare you?!
Saber! Don't let that sword—
Don't let that sword touch you!
That sword destroys magecraft.
It can sever a Master-Servant contract.
She's bad news...
I thought to settle this quickly...
Indeed, her magecraft would not work on Saber.
But what if her Master were caught in the blast?
Impossible.
It can't be!
What? What is that?
Tohsaka, look!
What in the world /is/ that?
A complex number space?
Impossible.
Impossible. Impossible!
Caster vanished?
Tohsaka!
Emiya-kun!
Shirou!
He didn't touch the main body.
It's more like he caught a fever.
Archer, do you know what that thing was?
Nope.
But that shadow is probably what's sucking mana out of the people of this city.
Shirou.
Emiya-kun, are you okay?
Yeah...
Looks like we can't prioritize our personal vendettas anymore.
Sakura, I'm sorry. I should have prevented this.
Let me see him.
All you're doing is hurting him.
So you came.
Apologies for calling you out here.
I arrived early, so I took the liberty of ordering a meal.
It's fine.
Want some?
Hell no!
Why did you call me here?
Emiya Shirou, what did you see last night?
You see, I have my own stake in this Holy Grail War.
Rin has reported to me about the incident at Ryuudou Temple.
We got into a fight with Matou Zouken.
He had Caster with him, but, uh...
It looked like he was puppeting her corpse.
So that old man has made his move...
Emiya Shirou.
Even Rin does not know this, but the night Caster was killed at Ryuudou Temple,
a single Servant left its bounded field.
Do you know which one?
No.
It was Assassin.
How do you know that?
My Servant, Lancer, saw it all.
I'm saying I was a Master, too.
Uh, crap... What's all this mean?
I had ordered Lancer to surveil Assassin.
He cornered him at Ryuudou Temple, but never returned.
Did Assassin kill him?
Assassins often rely on skills to erase their presence.
Their individual combat abilities are not high.
Lancer would never lose in conventional combat.
Emiya Shirou, you saw more last night than just Matou Zouken and Caster.
I wager that Assassin knew full well what he was doing when he lured Lancer.
What lurks there has turned against not just Servants, but the people of this city, as well.
If we liken Caster's absorption of mana to drawing blood,
that thing's methods are the act of consuming a meal.
If we let it roam free, this city will end up uninhabited.
Thirty people unconscious?
It happened on South Fourth Street in Miyama.
What exists there?
Ryuudou Temple...
What is the matter? Will you not eat?
I'd rather die than share a meal with you.
Sakura?
It's started snowing.
Hey, Sakura's at your place, right?
Huh?
Y-Yeah.
Okay, that's a relief.
That way, I won't run into her by accident.
I'm going after Zouken. I'll visit the Matou household.
That's...
I have history with the Matous.
You can leave the old-fashioned magecraft battle to me.
Hey, Emiya-kun.
What are you gonna do?
Saber-san, I don't know what you and Senpai are doing.
I don't think you'd tell me if I asked.
But Senpai came home injured last night.
I don't want Senpai to be in any danger.
I'm gonna go after that shadow.
We can't let it roam free.
It's already victimized the townspeople.
Oh?
Then I guess our ceasefire's continuing for a little longer.
Tohsaka...
We can't turn a blind eye to that shadow,
but don't bite off more than you can chew.
Not until we know what it is.
Yeah.
Sakura scolded me.
Last night, I wasn't capable enough to protect you.
I just went and collapsed on my own.
If there is a problem, it lies with me.
I cannot stop you from going to battle.
But I will fight by your side and protect you.
That is my duty.
For Sakura's sake, too.
What the heck?
Shirou!
Sa—
Shirou, it's Assassin!
You stay here!
Saber!
How very like you to come here.
Matou Zouken!
I will be in danger if I take that wind head-on.
Wind...
Rampage!
The blessing of wind protection.
It is indispensable for any who would cross the desert.
I care not if you refuse to approach,
but my lord is currently entertaining yours.
Fiend!
My job was only to draw your attention.
Assassin, you...
No Servant can resist that shadow.
One as pure as yourself will lose their mind from a single touch.
But first,
I will be taking your heart.
Trace on!
What can you do with a single flimsy stick?
Zabaniya.
Saber!
The strongest Servant, indeed.
She chose confronting her own darkness over having her heart stolen.
It appears things have been settled.
If you are a Master, you should know.
Your Servant has been obliterated from this world.
Bastard!
I leave this to you, Assassin.
Are you unhurt?
That is good.
Saber!
What the hell are you?
Oh. I guess this means
I'm officially not a Master anymore.
What is this?
He calls this a training ground?
This is... This /thing/ is...
Do you curse me?
Do you curse me for extending my rotting life with others' bodies?
No.
Your tenacity for survival is what makes you fit to be my lord.
There's a mischievous cat among us.
A cat?
Meow meow meow.
Sella, ready the car.
I'm going into the city tomorrow.
I don't know who you are,
but that belongs to the Einzberns.
Did I lose?
Is that...
Could it be?
Give it up.
It's the Holy Grail!
I must obtain it!
I told you to give it up.
Who are you? Why do you stand in my way?
Who am I?
You can tell at a glance, can you not?
Senpai...
Where have you been?
You got hurt again...
You need to take better care of yourself!
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
And...
I'm home, Sakura.
Yes.
Welcome back, Senpai.
Hey, Kiritsugu.
I don't get it.
What do I have to do to become a superhero?
I can't let it end here.
There's still someone I have to fight.
Senpai, I...
I thought maybe I could see you if I came here.
The Tohsakas had two children with an aptitude for magecraft.
This makes the second time I've received something from someone precious to me.
Take this opportunity to die, girl.
I promise. I'll...
23 - 18 Months Ago - Summer
37 - (Cut off at the top) Don't worry. Rest up and come back to club. -Taiga P.S. I'll come check on you later.
28 - Today's Headline - Fireworks Display Over the Ocean
48 - 15 Months Ago - Fall
57 - 14 Months Ago - Winter
20 - 10 Months Ago - Spring
51 - 3 Months Ago - Fall
47 - Suspect Flees From Car
Gas Leak in Shinto Office District
53 - The Present Day...
53 - Murder in Miyama-cho
30 - Student Council Room
03:51 - Another Gas Leak in Shinto Office District
04:25 - Ryuudou Issei-sama
Suzuki Tarou-sama
Takada Naoki-sama
59:22 - Preview
00:20 - In theaters 2018
Shirou Emiya is pretty good.
Isn't he?
And with Ayako Mitsuzuri and Shinji Matou,
we've got the Rookie Competition in the bag.
Yup!
But Fujimura-sensei, well...
Hmm?
Even among the first-years, Emiya feels kinda...
I dunno, different, I suppose?
I have a hard time pinning it down.
You got hurt at work right before the tournament?
The hell, man?
Swear to god. Everyone's gonna be
off their game now, You know that, right?
I'm sorry.
But you and Mitsuzuri should be
able to handle it, no sweat.
Sorry.
I'm home.
Commence tuning.
Analyzing base framework.
Analyzing component materials.
Altering base framework.
Reinforcing component materials.
Is it raining?
Aren't you Shinji's little sister?
Yes. My name is Matou Sakura.
Shirou! I'm here to check on you!
How are you holding up?
Uh, I can explain!
Look, it's not what it looks like!
I mean, I've been able to get by
on my own just fine, y'know?
I can hardly put my friend's sister to work now, can I?
As Shirou's guardian, I also have my reservations...
I help out with all the chores,
so it's okey-dokey here!
Oh, y'know, we just happened to run into each other!
Now, on to today's headlines—
The dishes go in the top cupboard.
The bottom one is for the rice, the knives, and, uh...
Whoa!
So you fold the shoulder around to the back,
line the sleeve up parallel to the crease,
and then you do the other side,
making sure it doesn't come unfolded...
Don't sweat it. Practice makes perfect.
This is good for now.
Let me try again.
All right, from the top.
I'll be on my way.
See ya tomorrows, Sakura-chan!
Oops.
Yeah, I remember now.
On that day a year and a half ago,
I lost to a really stubborn younger girl.
The season came and went.
But even after my shoulder healed,
my lifestyle remained the same.
I don't remember if it was Sakura's idea or mine.
Whoever's it was, it was probably pretty trivial.
If I had to name one thing that changed,
it'd be that I stopped going to club.
As for why, I wanted more time at work.
I was only ever in it to stay in shape anyway,
so it felt like a good enough opportunity to quit.
And, and this may seem
pretty minimal all things considered,
I'm home.
Welcome back, Senpai!
but I found myself using
my own key less and less often.
Ho-ho-ho! Merry Christmas!
Lemme tell ya...
Shirou was always trying to be just like Kiritsugu-san.
He'd keep shouting, "I'm gonna be a superhero!"
What's this about now? I swear, drunk people.
Kiritsugu-san was Senpai's father, yes?
Kiritsugu-san was like Shirou's hero.
No wonder he wanted to be just like him.
Surely you must have a hero
you look up to too, right?
My hero...
Senpai!
Hey, Emiya.
Oh. 'Sup, Issei.
Well, if it ain't Emiya!
Help us scout new members, will ya?
Hmm? Who's this?
Oh, this is Shinji's sister.
Ooh, for real?
Why, hello there!
You happen to be interested in archery?
Your brother does it,
so there's gotta be some interest, ye?
Oh, you are?
Sakura...
Sakura! Great!
How's it sound? Wanna join the archery club?
Or you got another club you wanna join?
N-No...
Perfecto! Come join us, then!
Geez. Pushy as ever.
What's wrong, Emiya?
Nothing...
Hey, Shirou!
Thanks a bunch, Sensei.
Aren't you a sensei, too?
Senpai?
Oh, it's nothing.
All right, smile, everyone!
Trace on.
Ugh, I have to take another one apart...
Oh. Again.
The flames lap away at my old memories,