Summer
A year and a half ago
Don't worry about club.
You can come back
once you get better.
Taiga
PS: I'll come check
up on you later!
Today's Topic
Fireworks Spectacle Over The Sea
Miyama Fireworks Festival
Yesterday, 8:00 PM
Autumn
A year and three months ago
Winter
A year and two months ago
Spring
Ten months ago
Autumn
Three months ago
One day ago
SUSPECT FLED FROM CAR WRECK
Today's Weather
GAS LEAK IN DOWNTOWN SHINTO
Present day
MURDERS IN MIYAMA TOWN
Today's Weather
Student Council Room
Quickly hydrates and
restores lost minerals.
Feel rejuvenated!
ANOTHER GAS LEAK IN DOWNTOWN SHINTO
Today's Weather
Ryuudou Issei
Suzuki Tarou
Takada Naoki
Kobayashi
Preview
In theaters